
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
        xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
        xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0"
	
xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#">
<channel>
  <title>RSS archive</title>
  <atom:link href="https://renegat0x0.ddns.net" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <link>https://renegat0x0.ddns.net/</link>
  <description>Link archive</description>
  <language>en-US</language>
<item><title>![CDATA[UK Woman Arrested For Filming Inside Empty Hospital]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-30 07:29:04+00:00</pubDate><link>https://summit.news/2020/12/30/uk-woman-arrested-for-filming-inside-empty-hospital/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://summit.news/2020/12/30/uk-woman-arrested-for-filming-inside-empty-hospital/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[UK: Only 377 people under 60 without preexisting conditions have died of COVID in Eng.]]</title><description>![CDATA[UK: Only 377 people under 60 without preexisting conditions have died of COVID in Eng.]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-26 21:03:33+00:00</pubDate><link>https://twitter.com/Fox_Claire/status/1342847212208984065</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://twitter.com/Fox_Claire/status/1342847212208984065</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Was 2020 A Simulation? (Science & Math of the Simulation Theory)]]</title><description>![CDATA[Was 2020 A Simulation? (Science & Math of the Simulation Theory)]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-26 07:46:46+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c9p9NE4Pji0</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c9p9NE4Pji0</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[A Complete Guide to LLVM for Programming Language Creators]]</title><description>![CDATA[A Complete Guide to LLVM for Programming Language Creators]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-24 10:04:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://mukulrathi.co.uk/create-your-own-programming-language/llvm-ir-cpp-api-tutorial/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://mukulrathi.co.uk/create-your-own-programming-language/llvm-ir-cpp-api-tutorial/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[WHO Deletes Naturally Acquired Immunity from Its Website]]</title><description>![CDATA[WHO Deletes Naturally Acquired Immunity from Its Website]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-23 11:38:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.aier.org/article/who-deletes-naturally-acquired-immunity-from-its-website/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.aier.org/article/who-deletes-naturally-acquired-immunity-from-its-website/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Writer Defends New Netflix Drama Bridgerton for Depicting Queen Charlotte as Black]]</title><description>![CDATA[Writer Defends New Netflix Drama Bridgerton for Depicting Queen Charlotte as Black]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-23 09:06:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://people.com/royals/writer-of-new-netflix-drama-bridgerton-defends-depicting-queen-charlotte-as-black/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://people.com/royals/writer-of-new-netflix-drama-bridgerton-defends-depicting-queen-charlotte-as-black/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Zoom Shared US User Data With Beijing]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-23 06:49:58+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.ntd.com/zoom-shared-us-user-data-with-beijing_544087.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ntd.com/zoom-shared-us-user-data-with-beijing_544087.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Coronavirus French Law Would Ban People Who Don’t Get COVID Vaccine From Using Public Transport]]</title><description>![CDATA[Coronavirus French Law Would Ban People Who Don’t Get COVID Vaccine From Using Public Transport]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-22 22:07:50+00:00</pubDate><link>https://summit.news/2020/12/22/french-law-would-ban-people-who-dont-get-covid-vaccine-from-using-public-transport/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://summit.news/2020/12/22/french-law-would-ban-people-who-dont-get-covid-vaccine-from-using-public-transport/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The Great Google Crash: The World’s Dependency Revealed]]</title><description>![CDATA[The Great Google Crash: The World’s Dependency Revealed]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-22 20:29:45+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vJ1cfb-5pHQ</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vJ1cfb-5pHQ</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Why is Facebook censoring private messages?]]</title><description>![CDATA[Why is Facebook censoring private messages?]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-22 14:19:18+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.quora.com/Why-is-Facebook-censoring-private-messages?share=1</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.quora.com/Why-is-Facebook-censoring-private-messages?share=1</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Biden receives first dose of Covid-19 vaccine on live television]]</title><description>![CDATA[President-elect Joe Biden received his first dose of the Pfizer and BioNTech coronavirus vaccine on live television Monday afternoon and reassured Americans of the vaccine's safety.]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-21 22:06:35+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/12/21/politics/bidens-coronavirus-vaccination/index.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cnn.com/2020/12/21/politics/bidens-coronavirus-vaccination/index.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[How does surveillance help make a smarter, safer city?]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-21 12:04:50+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.axis.com/blog/secure-insights/surveillance-smarter-safer-city/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.axis.com/blog/secure-insights/surveillance-smarter-safer-city/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Anti-lockdown protesters arrested as hundreds gather in central London just hours before tier 4 announcement]]</title><description>![CDATA[Anti-lockdown protesters arrested as hundreds gather in central London just hours before tier 4 announcement]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-20 10:16:49+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/anti-lockdown-protest-arrest-police-tier-4-b1776545.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/anti-lockdown-protest-arrest-police-tier-4-b1776545.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[WHO (finally) admits PCR tests create false positives]]</title><description>![CDATA[WHO (finally) admits PCR tests create false positives]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-18 21:59:35+00:00</pubDate><link>https://off-guardian.org/2020/12/18/who-finally-admits-pcr-tests-create-false-positives/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://off-guardian.org/2020/12/18/who-finally-admits-pcr-tests-create-false-positives/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Americans Can't Sue Pfizer, Moderna In Case of Covid-19 Vaccine Side Effects, Here's Why]]</title><description>![CDATA[Americans Can't Sue Pfizer, Moderna In Case of Covid-19 Vaccine Side Effects, Here's Why]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-18 18:13:12+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.news18.com/news/buzz/americans-cant-sue-pfizer-moderna-in-case-of-covid-19-vaccine-side-effects-heres-why-3190154.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.news18.com/news/buzz/americans-cant-sue-pfizer-moderna-in-case-of-covid-19-vaccine-side-effects-heres-why-3190154.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Nolte: Seattle Politician Calls Police She Defunded over Crime]]</title><description>![CDATA[Nolte: Seattle Politician Calls Police She Defunded over Crime]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-17 20:10:47+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/12/17/nolte-seattle-politician-calls-police-she-defunded-over-crime-she-wants-legalized/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/12/17/nolte-seattle-politician-calls-police-she-defunded-over-crime-she-wants-legalized/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[You can’t sue Pfizer or Moderna if you have severe Covid vaccine side effects. The government likely won't compensate you for damages either]]</title><description>![CDATA[You can’t sue Pfizer or Moderna if you have severe Covid vaccine side effects. The government likely won't compensate you for damages either]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-16 18:11:47+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/12/16/covid-vaccine-side-effects-compensation-lawsuit.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cnbc.com/2020/12/16/covid-vaccine-side-effects-compensation-lawsuit.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[WEF: Private Property And Privacy Will Vanish By 2030]]</title><description>![CDATA[WEF: Private Property And Privacy Will Vanish By 2030]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-14 18:04:34+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.technocracy.news/wef-private-property-and-privacy-will-vanish-by-2030/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.technocracy.news/wef-private-property-and-privacy-will-vanish-by-2030/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Command Line Bibles]]</title><description>![CDATA[<figure class="titleimg"><img src="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/deadsea-small.jpg" title="Where the Dead Sea Scrolls were found." /></figure>

<p>I've made a couple very useful command-line accessible Bibles for a
quick and scriptable lookup of Bible verses and passages. They exist not
only in English, but for Latin and Greek as well.</p>
<ol>
<li>English King James Version (including Apocrypha) &mdash;
<a href="https://github.com/lukesmithxyz/kjv">Github</a>,
<a href="https://gitlab.com/lukesmithxyz/kjv">Gitlab</a></li>
<li>Latin Vulgate &mdash; <a href="https://github.com/lukesmithxyz/vul">Github</a>, <a href="https://gitlab.com/lukesmithxyz/vul">Gitlab</a></li>
<li>Greek Septuagint &amp; New Testament &mdash;
<a href="https://github.com/lukesmithxyz/grb">Github</a>,
<a href="https://gitlab.com/lukesmithxyz/grb">Gitlab</a></li>
</ol>
<h2 id="installation">Installation</h2>
<pre><code>git clone https://github.com/lukesmithxyz/kjv.git
cd kjv
sudo make install
</code></pre>
<p>Or just replace <code>kjv</code> with <code>vul</code> for the Latin version or <code>grb</code> for the
Greek.</p>
<h2 id="usage">Usage</h2>
<h3 id="single-run">Single run</h3>
<p>Run the program name followed by a passage. The text will appear to you
in your pager. Arrows or vim-keys to scroll, <code>q</code> to quit.</p>
<pre><code>kjv rev 3:9
Revelation
3:9     Behold, I will make them of the synagogue of Satan, which say they are
        Jews, and are not, but do lie; behold, I will make them to come and
        worship before thy feet, and to know that I have loved thee.
</code></pre>
<p>Note that you may also give whole books or chapters. <code>kjv genesis</code> will
give you all of Genesis. <code>kjv mat 1:1-10</code> will show only Matthew 1:1-10.
Note also that you can usually abbreviate books.</p>
<h3 id="searching">Searching</h3>
<p><code>/</code> searches for patterns. For example, <code>kjv /offering</code> will search the
whole Bible for the word &quot;offering.&quot; You may specify a book/location
before it to search only that book.</p>
<h3 id="interactive-mode">Interactive mode</h3>
<p>Just type <code>kjv</code> (or <code>vul</code> or <code>grb</code>) alone to enter interactive mode. You
can then just type verses/books without prefixing them with the command
name each time if you prefer.</p>
<h2 id="origin">Origin</h2>
<p>I forked the original software from <a href="https://github.com/bontibon/kjv">this
repository</a> which is an incomplete
English King James Version (without the Apocrypha). With the use of
coreutils and vim, I found online texts of the Apochrypha, Vulgate,
Septuagint and the <a href="http://sblgnt.com/download/">SBL New Testament</a> and
formatting them to function with this program.</p>]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-11 00:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/command-line-bibles/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/command-line-bibles/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Only Use Old Computers!]]</title><description>![CDATA[<figure class="titleimg"><img src="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/dream_thinkpad_small.gif" title="If only ThiccPads were this THICC!" /><figcaption>The ideal ThiccPad</figcaption></figure>

<p>If there is a single point of advice I can offer novice computer users,
it is <em>stop using modern computers</em>.</p>
<p>If you look at &quot;technology YouTube,&quot;  by which I mean the massive multi-million subscriber channels, nearly all of
it is devoted to constantly reviewing and comparing every new computer,
processor, graphics card and product. There's big money in it because
obviously all of these companies put money in it, but also if you're a
normal person, you automatically assume you need the &quot;best&quot;
technology.</p>
<h2 id="do-you-need-a-modern-computer">Do you need a modern computer?</h2>
<p>Absolutely not. More than 95% of people could be using a computer from
2008 or before without any problems. Needing a recent machine is limited
to people who:</p>
<ol>
<li>Do extreme, professional, processor-intensive video-rendering.</li>
<li>Compile massive programs and operating systems with severe time constraints.</li>
<li>Play recent triple AAA video-games on high settings.</li>
<li>Use many massive Electron apps and other inexcusably bad software
written by soydevs and other people who shouldn't be writing
software.</li>
</ol>
<p>The last two reasons aren't really real reasons at all because they are
totally unnecessary and avoidable things.</p>
<p>But to the point, watching YouTube videos and using a word processor
does not require last month's new release.</p>
<p>Every video I upload, I transcode for settings optimal for YouTube,
meaning I render each video I record. On my computer from a decade ago,
that still takes only a couple minutes. A fancy $5000 computer might be
able to do it in less than one, but it is honestly not worth the pain
associated with modern computers.</p>
<h3 id="how-much-should-a-computer-cost-a-normal-person">How much should a computer cost a normal person?</h3>
<p>Either nothing or just around $200, I say. I use a ThinkPad X220 I got
for $90 on eBay. Before that, I used another ThinkPad X220 I also got
for $90. Like anything else, <strong>if you are buying things on Amazon,
you're doing it wrong</strong>.</p>
<h2 id="the-pain-of-modern-computers">The Pain of Modern Computers</h2>
<h3 id="modern-computers-are-more-breakable">Modern computers are more breakable</h3>
<p>As computing has become more and more popular, companies have started to
realize that a consumer's first reaction on having their $5 wifi card die is
immediately buy a whole new computer. This means two things: (1) they don't
bother to make computers easy to repair, in fact, they make it more difficult
and (2) there is absolutely no need to make computers durable at all. In fact,
it's probably better to let computers break so you'll get yet another sale.</p>
<p>Apple is by far the most anti-social computing company because of this.
I'll let the larger tech channels show you the specifics, but every
Apple product is brilliantly designed to make it difficult to fix very
basic and otherwise fixable problems. They have quite a racket licensing
out the ability and tools to companies that want to fix their terrible
hardware. Apple even used pentalobe screws just so normal people
couldn't open their computers up with a typical screwdriver. Of course
nowadays every other computer manufacturer imitates the Apple style
where apparent &quot;sleekness&quot; is supposed to be a signal of high quality.</p>
<h3 id="modern-computers-are-increasingly-monitoring-devices-and-come-with-proprietary-junk">Modern computers are increasingly monitoring devices and come with proprietary junk.</h3>
<h4 id="the-management-engine">The Management Engine</h4>
<p>You might've heard that all Intel i3/i5/i7 processors (that is, after
the Intel Core 2 Duo) have an onboard alternate processor that is meant
to function as spyware. This is called the Intel Management Engine. It
can view your memory and connect to the internet: basically all modern
computers have this permanent back door. In older computers, say the
ThinkPad X200, you can, with a little hardware action, remove the other
processor and replace the proprietary BIOS with
<a href="https://libreboot.org">Libreboot</a> or <a href="https://coreboot.org">Coreboot</a>,
but that is <em>not possible</em> on more modern computers (you can install
Coreboot on a more modern machine, but not all of the components of the
Management Engine are removed).</p>
<p>More recent computers, however are non-removable spyware by design and,
yes, the NSA can monitor any machine with a Management Engine. There are
actually even rumors that one of the taps that the FBI under the Obama
administration put on Trump during his campaign was a Management Engine
bug.</p>
<p>Note that AMD (Ryzen) processors have what they call a &quot;Platform
Security Processor&quot; that is equivalent to the Intel Management Engine,
so you're not escaping the issue by using one of them.</p>
<h4 id="nvidia">NVIDIA</h4>
<p>Again, unless you play modern videos alone all day, you literally have
no reason to have a modern computer, especially one with an expensive
graphics card. NVIDIA is a great example because they make graphics
cards and develop proprietary drivers for them to make it harder and
harder to use them on machines that aren't running whatever the most
recent spyware variant of Windows 10 is. Linux works perfectly on all
computers ancient and modern, but if you plug some NVIDIA thing up to
it, you might lose your screen or not be able to boot. A lot of gaymers
whine about their NVIDIA products &quot;not working&quot; on Linux without
realizing <strong>that is by design</strong>. NVIDIA and other companies and all CPU
designers go out of their way to keep their source code and standards
private which makes their products tangibly worse because it is harder
for other parties to write drivers for them. Why? Because most of them
have partnerships with Microsoft.</p>
<h3 id="the-problem-of-windows">The Problem of Windows</h3>
<p>How many times have you heard a normie explain to you that their
computer is slow because it's &quot;really old&quot; and they bought it &quot;way
back in 2015?&quot; It's an absurd statement of course. Computers don't
just get magically slow... <strong>...unless they've been running
Windows.</strong></p>
<p>In the future, once even Microsoft has switched over to a purely
Unix-based backend for their operating system, we're all going to have
a good laugh about how Microsoft Windows, <em>literally the worst and least
functioning operating system ever devised</em>, was the largest consumer
market share for decades.</p>
<p>I might go into how Windows is poorly designed in another page or video,
but I want to be clear that there is no such loss of speed on any Linux
distribution, which is what you should be using. I am one of the first
to complain about the feature bloat of the Linux kernel and Linux
software, but compared to Windows, it's no contest: <strong>Linux runs fast
on old hardware</strong>. You'll know from some of my videos, however, that
I'm not <em>big</em> into &quot;Linux Evangelism,&quot; mostly because it's sort of
strident and doesn't really work with a high success rate. Using Linux
is just something that normies have been immunized against (mostly
because &quot;It's what smart people do&quot;), but I always find myself in a
position where someone's Window installation has permanently crashed
and they're at the awkward decision of having to <em>buy a license</em> to
reinstall the dysfunctional and slow operating system they've grown to
hate.</p>
<p>There is quite literally no problem that normal people have with
computers that is not immediately alleviated by installing Linux.</p>
<h2 id="why-do-people-use-thinkpads">Why do people use ThinkPads?</h2>
<p>As I said above, I use a X220 ThinkPad. Older ThinkPads are fairly popular among people who think and care about doing things effectively and economically on a computer. Why is this?</p>
<p>ThinkPads were always designed for enterprise environments, meaning the financial incentives for the manufacturer are not always planned obsolesce, but a long-standing reputation among large companies of having durable, fixable and expandable machines.</p>
<p>To replace a hard drive on the X200 requires unscrewing just a single screw. Same to replace the memory. To replace a spoiled keyboard is no more than three screws.
Modern laptops, including the degraded modern ThinkPad have abandoned this simplicity and opt for the Apple-Mac/cell phone design technique of making batteries, memory and the rest functionally soldered and irremovable.</p>
<h3 id="how-far-can-500-go">How far can $500 go?</h3>
<p>Over the years, I&rsquo;ve had many things break on my laptops, but since I&rsquo;ve been using ThinkPads, it is incredibly easy to keep a working computer even after rough use. I estimate that I have never spent more than a combined total of $500 on computers, which is usually a bare minimum for what someone can buy a &ldquo;modern&rdquo; laptop for nowadays.</p>
<p>When the keyboard on my ThinkPad breaks, I can just buy a replacement keyboard for $30 or $40 and replace the old one much easier than any other model. That&rsquo;s the modularity of these computers.</p>
<p>Even in the worst case scenario when something on the motherboard makes the computer unbootable, I still get to keep my &ldquo;broken&rdquo; ThinkPad and repurpose the memory, wifi card, keyboard and everything else. I still have some parts of every laptop I&rsquo;ve had just because they do come in a lot of use. The other month, a friend&rsquo;s wifi on his desktop went out and I could replace it with one of my old ThinkPad modules.</p>
<p>This is the kind of thing you lose with modern computers. This is purposeful on the part of manufacturers, and it&rsquo;s important not to pay them huge amounts of money to incentivize this behavior. It&rsquo;s very easy to live off of 10 year old computers nowadays. The eBay-and-etc resale market is massive even thought many of us have gotten wise to the value of these old computers.</p>]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-11 00:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/only-use-old-computers/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/only-use-old-computers/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Science vs. Soyence]]</title><description>![CDATA[<figure class="titleimg"><img src="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/soyence.jpg" /></figure>

<p>There's nothing necessarily <em>wrong</em> with science, reason, knowledge
etc. To some degree, they're fundamental for survival in this world in
one way or another. But one of the more worrisome problems which have
arisen since the Enlightenment, and especially in the past several
years, is the fact that whenever scientific knowledge has increased,
human arrogance has accelerated even faster. This isn't a metaphysical,
moral arrogance; it's one that is more and more jeopardizing the human
cosmos.</p>
<p>We live in a pop-scientific and pop-technological world. Because common
people are constantly weighing themselves down with new gadgets and
state-of-the-art genetically engineered food, there's a tendency to
want to pay homage to the amorphous blob of &quot;knowledge.&quot; Of course,
much like the Greek Gods, we cannot seem to speak to &quot;knowledge&quot;
directly, or to mentally murky academics, but only to official
mediators: journalists and &quot;science communicators&quot; and the like.</p>
<p>The religious metaphor is intentional. Of course the actual view of
Popperian science is that scientific &quot;advancement&quot; is less of an
increase in knowledge than a decrease in falsity. We can never be sure
of what is true, but we can gradually establish what is false and
contradictory; science does exclusively the latter. Real scientific work
refutes and calls into question established fact and is in a constant
self-regeneration. Facts mean nothing in themselves.</p>
<p>And scientific models, from our models of the atom, to models of the
Earth's weather and climate, to models of our body are highly
circumstantial, and as a rule, will nearly all inevitably be proven
false. Theories are the narratives we cast over facts which have not yet
been ruled false. We know nearly nothing of how the brain works. Sure,
we know there are synapses, and we know what brains end up doing in some
circumstances, but we haven't begun to scratch the surface of how a
brain is actually engineered (computational models be damned). The same
is true of the human body and is especially true of human society.</p>
<p>Now Neil deGrasse Tyson has the annoying mantra that he repeats at every
possible opportunity, which goes something like: &quot;the good thing about
science is that it's true whether or not you believe in it.&quot; First
off, I don't know what's good about that; it'd be pretty damn
convenient to live in a world where we could imagine away gravity or CO2
or cancer, but aside from this, science, actual science as a critical
methodology is manifestly <em>not</em> true and is <em>not</em> the truth. Science is
a way of marginally approaching truth by discovering falsity, and in
most endeavors, this approachment is so marginal as to be inert in all
our daily lives. There is nothing to &quot;believe in&quot; in science anyway,
because it's an exposer of <em>non</em>-truth.</p>
<p>But in pop-science, Science<sup>®</sup> is &quot;knowledge&quot; and deviation from the
scientific catechism is &quot;irrational.&quot; It's not just irrational to
dispute consensus, but irrational to <em>fail to implement it in your
personal life</em>.</p>
<h2 id="in-practice">In Practice</h2>
<p>The greatest danger of pop-science is the unquestioned assumption that
life should be led &quot;scientifically.&quot; That we should &quot;look for
evidence,&quot; &quot;question everything,&quot; and universally &quot;challenge
authority&quot; (unless that authority is a professor). The problem should
be blatantly obvious in hindsight.</p>
<p>An obvious example: in the 20th century, Western societies had to deal
with the very real problem of a bizarre increase in lung cancer rates.
We &quot;know&quot; now that smoking tobacco and other substances apparently
cause drastically higher lung cancer rates, but this was lost on the
people at the time.</p>
<p>The relationship between smoking and cancer was highly circumstantial;
there were some statistical correlations established, but as any
pop-science guru will tell us &quot;correlation is not causation!&quot; For
decades, scientifically minded people looked for evidence while millions
more died. Smoking companies took refuge in the fact that there was no
<em>mechanism</em> understood behind how smoking could cause lung cancer. With
all scientific rigor, they insisted for decades that the increase in
lung cancer was due to something else, or merely an increase in
diagnosis capacity. And <em>they were on the side of scientific
skepticism!</em></p>
<p>Only now that there is some understanding of how carcinogens in smoke
can damage the lungs can we say that the &quot;scientific consensus&quot; is
that smoking causes lung cancer. Cute, but if people had been
<em>&quot;irrationally&quot; cautious</em>, the human tragedy would've been
substantially mitigated.</p>
<p>The problem is that &quot;looking for evidence&quot; before acting or non-acting
is personally and socially dangerous. In nearly all circumstances, our
intuition (crafted by millions of years of evolution) or social norms
(which keep us to established safe routes) are much better guides to
life than the scientific consensus, despite them being &quot;irrational&quot;
(and sorry, religion is part of this too). When someone guzzles down
some newly fabricated energy drink or gallons of soda, they're nearly
certainly damaging their bodies in ways science does not yet understand.
Don't wait 40 years for some longitudinal peer-reviewed study to prove
that eating plastic is bad for you. Trust your instincts before you give
credence to some YouTuber who says inane things like &quot;There's no
evidence that...&quot;</p>
<p>My favorite little &quot;irrationality&quot; that we all commit is of course,
sleep. After millennia of trying to understand it, there is no
established scientific reason or justification for why humans &quot;need&quot;
sleep. Sure there are hypotheses (memory processing, repair, maybe even
something Freudian), but none close to common currency. In the words of
one of the world's most prominent sleep researchers, William Denent,
&quot;As far as I know, the only reason we need to sleep that is really,
really solid is because we get sleepy.&quot; Of course the absence of
logical evidence to the necessity of sleep keeps no NdGT fan from
wasting their time on the &quot;Bronze-Age Myth&quot; of the importance of
sleep.</p>
<h2 id="not-mis-understanding-complex-systems">(Not) (Mis-)Understanding Complex Systems</h2>
<p>The human body is a complex system in which every &quot;system&quot; is
overlapping, somewhat redundant, all-affecting and fundamentally beyond
linear analysis. Our scientific studies can find binary variables that
correlate with a low <em>p</em> value, but that tells us nothings about what's
actually going on and nothing about the underlying mechanisms. Again,
the same is true of the human brain and the same is true of human
<em>society</em>. Nothing is a simple input-output system.</p>
<p>What this means is that basically nothing from the world of pop-science
can <em>ever</em> affect the basics of our lives because the interaction of our
component parts are just non-amenable to any kind of generalizations
that make intuitive sense to us. Everything we do affects our bodies in
ways we can't predict so the proper strategy is always an
&quot;irrational&quot; precaution and avoidance of novelty.</p>
<p>Things, of course, get especially touchy when talking about the
&quot;rational&quot; management of society. Every good denizen of the
post-Enlightenment world, even most of those on the &quot;Right&quot; have the
idea that the economy and social relationships are simple one-to-one
hydraulic systems that can be managed like a little steam engine. Now
we've been rationally managed to hell and not back (and the solution is
always more rational management).</p>
<p>The terrible truth is that traditional social norms are <em>irrational</em> and
<em>still do</em> exist for a reason in the perennial gale of social evolution.
Social change and social progress (note the lack of scare quotes) have
always been happening, but only now do we have the naive idea that the
units of society (people) have the competence to design and contribute
to an otherwise unconscious evolution of social memes.</p>
<p>Anyway, I'll give the last word on this issue to Noam Chomsky, who
somehow manages to say something clear and admirable on the subject:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&ldquo;Science is a very strange activity. It only works for simple
problems. Even in the hard sciences, when you move beyond the simplest
structures, it becomes very descriptive. By the time you get to big
molecules, for example, you are mostly describing things. The idea
that deep scientific analysis tells you something about problems of
human beings and our lives and our inter-relations with one another
and so on is mostly pretense in my opinion&mdash;self-serving pretense
which is itself a technique of domination and exploitation and should
be avoided. Professionals certainly have the responsibility of not
making people believe that they have some special knowledge that
others can't attain without special means or special college
education or whatever. If things are simple, they should be said
simply; if there is something serious to say that is not simple, then,
fine, that's good and interesting. We can perhaps find deep answers
to certain questions that do bear directly on issues of human interest
and concern, but that is rarely true.&rdquo;</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="science-communicators">&quot;'Science' 'Communicators'&quot;</h2>
<p>One of the worst aspects of all of this is that this understanding of
pop-science encourages people to distrust what they know or can judge of
the world in favor of the caricature of the consensus of
institutionalized academics. People have this idea that there are these
intellectual, peer-reviewed demigods in universities who discover the
secrets to the universe and communicate them through their messengers
stationed at BuzzFeed and the Huffington Post. Betraying their infinite
wisdom would make you &quot;irrational&quot; or a &quot;fundie.&quot; The reality is
that these demigods really just went to graduate school because they
were lazy and initiativeless, and even in the abstract, most of their
real work has nothing to do with your life whatsoever. It's only the
messengers that convince you of that because it stimulates their power
trip.</p>
<p>Science journalists, much like journalists generally, are people too
incompetent and emotional to work in the private sector, too dumb to be
academics (and the standards are abysmally low these days), too full of
themselves to work in charity and too bumbling, weak and arrogant to
work in a blue collar or manual occupation. Journalism is an attractive
career to many because it demands the least rigor and honor and promises
the greatest power and influence.</p>
<p>Their self-ordained duty is to overwhelm the public with a confusion of
&quot;studies&quot; that increasingly seem to micromanage a neurotic person's
life. &quot;Studies show that&quot; classical music may help infant brain
growth, or that gluten ravages the intestines, or that simply owning
more books causes higher scholastic achievement, or that Vitamin C or
antioxidants or kale or whatever health-food <em>de jour</em> solve all the
world's problems.</p>
<p>At the end of the day, the worst part is that we talk about &quot;science&quot;
as if it's some kind of anthropomophic creature with desires and
feelings and a plan for us all. It's a uniquely modern flaw to say
things like, &quot;Science tells us that...&quot; &quot;Science is about..&quot;
&quot;Science is against...&quot; Does this not strike anyone else as creepy?
The interpretation of science forced on the public is a scriptural one,
where law to live life by are codified in &quot;peer-reviewed&quot; journals and
communicated by intermediaries. 'Science's' purview is infinite and
any failure to conform is some congenital failure or reason.</p>]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-11 00:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/science-vs-soyence/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/science-vs-soyence/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The Fragility of Physics]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>Physics has a reputation of being a uniquely &quot;scientific&quot; field. In
other fields, you might hear of the concept of &quot;Physics Envy&quot; which is
supposed to be a deep-seated desire of academics of other disciplines
for the rigorousness and elegance of physics. Only physics, so the
popular understanding goes, is truly able to abstract away from the
messiness of detail and create truly beautiful and solvent models of
their subject matters. Physics is thus the queen of the &quot;hard
sciences.&quot;</p>
<p>I object to the very idea of &quot;hard vs. soft sciences&quot; for reasons that
will soon be clear, but I think it is most important to remember that
for all its pretensions, <strong>physics is the most fragile science</strong>. That
isn't necessarily <em>bad</em>, but it's true.</p>
<h2 id="why-fragile">Why &quot;fragile?&quot;</h2>

<figure class="resright"><img src="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/purity_theology.jpg" title="The purity of theology" /></figure>

<p>Put simply, physics, partially due to its somewhat abstract nature, is
exactly that domain where our interpretation of the universe is <em>most
likely</em> to change <em>radically</em> in the event of any kind of theoretical
sea change. That is, while in other more terrestrial sciences, the data
is well-known and the theory is in debate, in physics, the opposite is
arguably true. In astrophysics, quantum mechanics, the study of gravity
or relativity, this should all be obvious.</p>
<p>Even without departing the cuddling embrace of mainstream physics, we
can actually see this clearly. What is the ultimate fate of the universe
to be? A continuous expansion of the universe until heat death? Perhaps
gravity or some other force will pull everything back in a Big Crunch?
The correct alternative is a statement of very specific and tendentious
data which changes quite a great deal with any kind of new
interpretations of what we see.</p>
<p>It's worth it to remember that for most of man's history, including
the initial development of what we nowadays call physics, the &quot;normal
state&quot; of the universe was assumed to be the state of affairs we're
familiar with on the surface of the Earth: everything falls down to the
ground and things propelled in space will slow down until they stop.</p>
<p>But modern physics now looks at the nature of our life on Earth as an
exception to the general rule of frictionless and continuous movement in
the vacuum of space. A valid question to ask is <em>how much more that we
take to be normal is a special case of reality?</em> As we encounter more
and more abberrant data, such as quantum mechanics, we might soon find
ourself unifying seemingly disparate forces in the same was that Newton
in a novel and seemingly absurd way the fact that objects fall to the
ground with the apparent fact that the Earth orbits the Sun into one new
concept: <em>Gravity</em>. Such a unification religates all our universals to a
special case.</p>
<h3 id="does-light-really-go-the-speed-of-light">Does light really go the speed of light?</h3>
<p>Physics is fragile because it is like a game of Jenga. Pull out or
change one piece and the whole thing is either reordered or simply
collapses.</p>
<p>As an example, say that within several years, we realize that the speed
of light, for some known or unknown reason, doesn't function with the
universality we assumed. Suppose that there is some kind of interaction
of light and gravity such that light is faster in some parts of the
universe. The reason isn't important. Or suppose we merely find out
that in the past, there has been a systematic principle (similar to the
Heisenberg Principle) that has miscalibrated all of our measurements of
light.</p>
<p>Even if we have minutely mismeasured, the Jenga piece of light will
radically alter everthing: our ideas of how old the universe is, our
relationships with other planets, the solvency of general relativity,
etc. You might say that there is a &quot;concordance of evidence&quot; that
attests to our single known speed of light, but another way of putting
that is that we have many other things tied into our interpretation of
light that will have to change if we realize our models of it are
flawed.</p>
<h3 id="poverty-of-data">Poverty of data</h3>
<p>Especially in the astronomical domain, it's worth remembering exactly
how circumstantial our ideas of space are. We sometime speak of the
traits of other solar systems' planets as if we've been there. But in
reality, astrophysicists guess the chemical compositions of foreign
planets based on their light frequencies and other fragile data. Any
systematic error in observation over those thousands or millions of
lightyears and we have been counting angels on pinheads the whole time.</p>
<p>People have the idea that because astrophysicists make extraordinary
claims about planets, galaxies and time periods far beyond our mortal
ken that they must have extraordinary evidence for them. That is frankly
not the case. We have a piece-meal and jury-rigged set of circumstantial
reasoning leading us to these claims. Seeing them computerized in full
color in a science documentary doesn't make them more real. It just
makes them look more official.</p>
<h2 id="physics-vs-soft-sciences">Physics vs. &quot;soft sciences&quot;</h2>
<p>I remember talking to someone over the internet who accused me of having
a low view of institutionalized science and being a dreaded
epistemological anarchist because one of my degrees is in the &quot;soft
science&quot; of linguistics. While I have a lot of bad things to say about
the current state of linguistics, as a field, it is substantially more
advanced and its findings are substantially more solid than physics. At
that, formalizing ideas in math doesn't just make something a better or
a more rigorous science anyway, which is the assumption of many people
have.</p>
<p>While linguistics undergoes theoretical changes every several
generations, the <em>data</em>, or really more importantly <em>the phenomenology</em>
of linguistics is as secure as ever across all theoretical frameworks.
That is, we know how language works. We can see abstract relationships
between morphemes and syntactic structure. Even if we totally rewrite
our narratives and theories about linguistic basics, there is no debate
about the structure of language and how basic data relates to other
data. This is absolutely the opposite of physics.</p>
<p>Physics is pretty solid on earth, and solid when you are running objects
at each other in a vacuum, but once we broach the territory of
astrophysics, relativity, gravity and more or less <em>anything else that
we as humans lack direct intuition of</em> most of the &quot;facts&quot; of physics
are theory-internal facts, and will fade away or be rendered obsolete
when the next theoretical fad comes around.</p>
<h2 id="my-standard-for-theoretical-frameworks">My standard for theoretical frameworks</h2>
<p>I think any serious scholar needs the ability to operate cognitively
with multiple different theoretical frameworks in mind.</p>
<p>For example, (on linguistics) I don't really take Generative Grammar
very seriously, in fact, despite it being on of the most well-funded
dialects of linguistics nowadays, it's pretty inert. Despite that, I
view it as very important for me to be able to process linguistic
problems within Generative Grammar and word explanations within its
ideas. It's nice to be able to say to someone &quot;this alternation is
accounted for if this DP occupies the spec of CP.&quot; I don't <em>believe</em>
in CPs or specifiers as being psychologically real, but I can recognize
the language as communicative.</p>
<p><strong>A good theoretical framework is one that can produce facts and
observations that can be recognized and explained outside of its
framework as well.</strong></p>
<p>That is, a framework should cue us in to finding utterly novel
observations and thus a new <em>phenomenology</em>. This goes against the
egocentric motivations of a lot of scientific frameworks whose
practitioners are trying to edge out &quot;the competition.&quot; Fields that
spend most of their time trying to formalize previous observations
within their own theoretical language are mostly a waste of time (this
is Generative Grammar, frankly, although due to historical ignorance,
many people in GG do not know they are re-treading steps).</p>
<p>One of the biggest issues of modern post-war institutionalized science
is that the funding and peer-review mechanism is self-reinforcing: all
fields converge to be &quot;unipolar&quot;: only one methodology or framework is
deemed &quot;scientific.&quot; This creates a community of &quot;scientists&quot; who
are more an more incestuous and generally oblivious not just to other
possibilities of inquiry, but don't even have to be aware of their own
priors or assumptions.</p>
<h2 id="the-blinders-of-positivism">The blinders of positivism</h2>
<p>As I've interacted with physicists more, I'm often <em>surprised</em> by how
irrelevant they think even the most basic theoretical awareness is.
That's &quot;philosophy&quot; for them. It's not uncommon to hear zingers like
these:</p>
<ol>
<li>&quot;Science isn't about truth, it's about creating models.&quot;</li>
<li>&quot;Physics is about fitting equations.&quot;</li>
<li>&quot;We don't do philosophy.&quot;</li>
</ol>
<p>Things like these are said as if they are some kind of statement of
universal and well-consented-to truth, when in reality they are absurd
Zen koans of the positivist religion. This was a loony opinion a hundred
years ago and people saying these things now <em>know</em> that they are
ludicrous. They have just become identifying marks of the social club.</p>
<p>Yep, science is about creating models... models that replicate reality,
i.e. <em>Truth</em>.</p>
<p>A scientists who doesn't do philosophy isn't a scientist: he's a
meter-reader. A philosopher who doesn't do science isn't a
philosopher: he's just a stoner. The attempt to sever these two words
from each other is part of the problem.</p>
<p>Physicists seem to be particularly touchy on this point. On one hand,
they insist that philosophy is &quot;not their thing&quot; and &quot;not related.&quot;
On the other hand, they get incredibly angry when <em>anyone else</em> dares to
either put the methodology of modern physics to any kind of
philosophical tests <em>or even</em> to look into philosophical ramifications
of their work.</p>
<p>In reality, modern scientists and positivists have their own
metaphysics, it is just an <em>implicit</em> one that they advertently or
inadvertently sneak into their theories. They can only do it because its
clumsy sterile &quot;materialism&quot; is the background-radiation of the modern
world.</p>]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-11 00:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/the-fragility-of-physics/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/the-fragility-of-physics/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Why I Use the GPL and Not Cuck Licenses]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>Every piece of software I write I license under the <a href="https://www.gnu.org/licenses/quick-guide-gplv3.html">GNU Public License
Version 3</a> (GPLv3)
unless I have forked it from something else.</p>
<p>The GPLv3 is the premiere <em>copyleft</em> license, meaning that it not
only allows users to run, modify and distribute their own versions of
what I write, but it also requires that no one in that chain of
development restrict and close-source that software: it and software
deriving from it must forever remain open, usable and sharable. Richard
Stallman, one of the minds behind the GPL has described it as a &quot;hack&quot;
of the copyright system because it uses the legal infrastructure of
copyright to ensure software is free rather than restricted.</p>
<p>But occasionally I get asked why I don't use so-called <em>permissive licenses</em> like BSD or MIT. These are free software licenses, but
they <em>do not</em> require that forked versions of the code be free and open
source software. In other words, you can take something written with a
BSD or MIT license, put it in the next version of Windows and no one
will ever know. If you did that with GPL code, you'd be in for big
legal trouble if found out.</p>
<p>I and others have recently taken to calling these permissive licenses
<em>Cuck Licenses</em>.</p>
<h2 id="why-cuck-licenses">Why &quot;Cuck Licenses?&quot;</h2>
<p>Why be mean and bully BSD and MIT licenses calling them &quot;Cuck
Licenses?&quot;</p>
<p>Quite simply, using them is precisely analogous to being cuckolded. When
you really look at it, the similarity is uncanny.</p>
<p>I understand GPL free software and its ethical vision for software. I
also understand that desire for people and businesses to <em>not</em> release
their source code for commercial and monetary benefits. What I don't
understand is simultaneously releasing free code with no requirement
that it remain free. It can now be used against you and others&mdash;if you
had moral qualms about that, you could've <em>at least</em> made money off of
it yourself.</p>
<p>Using a Cuck License <em>especially</em> for &quot;ethical reasons&quot; or &quot;because I
like open source software&quot; is beyond absurd. You're simply writing
code and effectively abandoning the privileges of intellectual property
while allowing any large corporation to come and close-source and
monetize your software and sell it back to you without any other
obligations. You have also abandoned your ability to ever complain about
IBM, Microsoft, Apple or any other tech giant because <strong>you are
literally writing their proprietary software</strong>. These companies even
sometimes take very simple code from minor projects and use it to save a
buck and a little effort.</p>

<figure class="resright"><a href="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/timnolet.png"><img src="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/timnolet.png" title="'Noooo! You can't use my heckin' code that I legally gave you the right to use!'" /></a><figcaption>When you license with a permissive license, you don't have a say anymore.</figcaption></figure>

<p>At the end of the day, using a Cuck License is little different from
either releasing software in the public domain or just not licensing it
(in some jurisdictions, at least). It has the pretense of a license, but
for no real function. I suppose depending on which you use, you at least
get your name on the license, but I hardly think that that's how
internet fame and glory is actually distributed anyway. As far as I'm
concerned <strong>using a Cuck License is worse for user freedom than just
releasing it in the public domain</strong>. This is because at least public
domain software can be taken and later additions can be protected by the
GPL. The legal case for doing that with a Cuck License is not so clear.</p>
<h3 id="no-whiners">No whiners!</h3>
<p>The funniest thing is when Cuck Licensers <em>complain</em> that people are
abiding by their licenses. They will <em>complain</em> that people took their
code and made money off of it. They will <em>complain</em> when they don't get
some social credit they feel like they deserve when their code is used
in a project. They will <em>complain</em> if people fork their project and it
becomes more popular than the original. They will <em>complain</em> when some
tech giant takes their code and makes spyware out of it.</p>
<p>If they were serious about stopping any of this, <em>they easily could've
by licensing their project as anything other than a code giveaway</em>. If
you want praise for some contribution, put it in the license. If you
don't want your software used for proprietary software, use the GPLv3.</p>
<h2 id="a-cuck-licenser-gets-what-he-deserves-and-we-all-pay-the-price">A Cuck Licenser gets what he deserves (and we all pay the price).</h2>
<p>One of the funniest and saddest horror stories of Cuck Licenses I can
think of is Andrew Tanenbaum, who released MINIX, an operating system,
under a BSD license. Intel silently took this software (thanks to its
license) and unbeknownst to him, used it for their Intel Management
Engine, <strong>making it the OS of the spyware microprocessor/backdoor now
running in all Intel CPUs</strong>. We all have a permanent NSA backdoor
because of the Intel Management Engine&mdash;all made possibly by Cuck
License cuckery.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cs.vu.nl/~ast/intel/">Only many, many years later was this even revealed to
Tanenbaum.</a> Read that blog post of his
as he slowly externalizes his mixed feelings, tinged with guilt. After
all, on the &quot;bright&quot; side, he says:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&quot;I guess that makes MINIX the most widely used computer operating
system in the world, even more than Windows, Linux, or MacOS.&quot;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Wow, what a proud achievement. But regardless, Tanenbaum already feels
some regret about the fact that his permissive license allowed Intel to
withhold this:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&quot;This was a complete surprise. I don't mind, of course, and was not
expecting any kind of payment since that is not required. There isn't
even any suggestion in the license that it would be appreciated.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>&quot;The
only thing that would have been nice is that after the project had
been finished and the chip deployed, that someone from Intel would
have told me, just as a courtesy, that MINIX was now probably the most
widely used operating system in the world on x86 computers. That
certainly wasn't required in any way, but I think it would have been
polite to give me a heads up, that's all.&quot;</p>
</blockquote>

<figure class="resright"><img src="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/cia.png" title="A glow-in-the-dark CIA gamer" /></figure>

<p>You can feel the regret. <strong>With Cuck Licenses, you get the worst of two
worlds:</strong> You get no credit for your work, nor money for licensing fees
like other proprietary software and your software will be used to
violate your and other users' privacy when it is used in closed-source
environments. Oh, no... copes incoming:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&quot;Many people (including me) <strong>don't like the idea of an all-powerful
management engine in there at all</strong> (since it is a possible security
hole and a dangerous idea in the first place), but that is Intel's
business decision and a separate issue from the code it runs. A
company as big as Intel could obviously write its own OS if it had
to.&quot; <em>emphasis added</em></p>
</blockquote>
<p>If Tanenbaum had released MINIX under the GPL, we <em>wouldn't be</em> at the
mercy of Intel's business decision. They would've had to release the
source code for the microprocessor, keeping user privacy ensured and
irradicating the permanent spyware liability all computers have
nowadays.</p>
<p>If they wouldn't want to do that, they'd have to just write an
operating system themselves. Tanenbaum is right, they obviously
<em>could've</em> taken the time and money to write an OS themselves if they
had to, but they <em>didn't have to</em>, <strong>because a BSD license cuck wrote
it for them</strong>. Thanks a lot, sucker! Now our computers are being
monitored at a lower start-up cost and we have you to thank. It
would've been a lot <em>more</em> respectable to <em>not</em> use a permissive
license and instead license it proprietarily if he has no moral issues
with proprietary software: he could've <em>at least</em> gotten Intel to pay
him to use his operating system. Heck, if he had used the GPL and if
they took it anyway, he could become an insta-millionaire by suing them
right now.</p>
<p>The moral of the story is perhaps lost on Tanenbaum, who finishes up his
blog post with:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&quot;If nothing else, this bit of news reaffirms my view that the
Berkeley license provides the maximum amount of freedom to potential
users.&quot;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>&quot;Maximum amount of freedom to potential users&quot; is somehow
mass-surveilance of every computer user thanks to the BSD license.
Thanks for your contribution to &quot;freedom.&quot;</p>
<h2 id="the-freedom-that-cuck-licenses-preserve">The Freedom that Cuck Licenses &quot;preserve&quot;</h2>
<p>&quot;Freedom&quot; is an incoherent buzzword if you don't define it. There are
some people who might argue that the fact that they can't kill and
steal freely is a violation of their &quot;freedom.&quot; That's very true in
some sense.</p>
<p>In the same way, the GPL (unlike Cuck Licenses) &quot;violates&quot; the freedom
of all people to close-source code and hide it from the public and (in
effect) do annoying or privacy-violating things with it.</p>
<p>The goal of the Free Software Movement, defended by copyleft licenses
like the GPL is for all software writers and users to live in an
environment of publicly auditable, editable and exchangable code. The
goals of the Open Source movement have a similar goal, albeit often
guided by practical considerations.</p>

<figure class="resright"><img alt="Cuck-licensers write proprietary software for free." src="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/janny.jpg" /><figcaption>He does it for free.</figcaption></figure>

<p>Cuck Licenses, however, undermine those goals. They will <em>say</em> that they
maximize freedom by placing no requirement on those who distribute When
you release any code under a Cuck License, you are simply writing free
commercial code for corporations that will inevitably use it against
you. You might as well just <em>actually get a job with them</em> so you can
get paid for what you do instead of just getting cucked. When you
release code under the GPL, you write free software that benefits other
people who write free software.</p>
<p>The Free Software Foundation and the GPL people have correctly realized
that just being &quot;permissive&quot; with licenses is unworkable in the
current environment. The legal infrastructure incentivizes and defends
proprietary software and gives it a systematic financial advantage. The
GPL is a viral antidote to that. Obviously if all software were free and
no laws protected &quot;intellectual property&quot; in publicly obtainable
software, <em>everything</em> would be &quot;permissively licensed.&quot; We don't
live in that world. The GPL and other &quot;copyleft&quot; licenses are ways of
undermining and disincentivizing and making impossible the
close-sourcing of software. Not using the GPL and using a cuck license
is just the same as writing proprietary because <em>you literally are</em>
because all of your software can be snatched up and proprietarily
licensed.</p>
<h2 id="bbuut-the-gpl-isnt-enforceable">&ldquo;B...buut the GPL isn't enforceable!&rdquo;</h2>
<p>I've heard some people pass around the idea that somehow the GPL is
unenforceable. After all, if you have close source software, how can
anyone really tell what's going on? In some cases, that might be true
if you have perfect op-sec. That wouldn't be the case for the Intel
Management Engine above, and that wouldn't be the case for Windows XP,
whose source code recently leaked.</p>
<p>I have known people in industry writing proprietary software and
worrying about the GPL is real. The &quot;virus&quot; of GPL taking over
everything and making it free is something people have to take heed of.
I'm sure there is some level of GPL-violation going on in some places
at least, just because lifting simple routines or copy-and-pasting some
things from GPL with significant enough changes could go unseen even if
leaked, but integrating larger GPL programs would be nearly an
impossibility.</p>
<p>At the end of the day, though, what does it matter? What is a totally
unenforced GPL? It's just a Cuck License&mdash;Isn't that what license
cucks want? So why should they care? At their very best, BSD and MIT
licenses are only what GPL might be at its very worst.</p>
<p>The GPL is a permanent liability for any company that crosses it. Some
companies might be so bold to lift GPL code and hide it, but there is
always a risk and a worry that prevents its general violation.</p>
<h2 id="addendum">Addendum</h2>
<h3 id="are-copyleft-licenses-always-best-even-for-freedom">Are copyleft licenses always best even for freedom?</h3>
<p>No!</p>
<p>Here's a question I got about this article that I'll reproduce here
because it touches on something good.</p>
<blockquote>
<pre><code>[personal details omitted for anonymity]

However, I read your article, and I can see your point. I have an idea for an
Operating System and due to your arguments, I would definitely license that
under the GPL, as well as any new programs I write. I might even change most or
all of my current programs to GPL, with the exception of that bc, which needs
to remain BSD since it is default in FreeBSD now.

That said, I have a library I am working on, and my experience is that
libraries under the GPL do not get used, unless a commercial license is offered
as well, and often, not even then. You can see this with glibc, which has a
special linking exception and the fact that the LGPL is fairly popular for
libraries.

First question: what is your opinion on the linking exception and the LGPL? Are
they Cuck Licenses? I mean, they do require that the library and any
modifications be put under the LGPL, which means that the library remains libre
software. However, they can also be put into proprietary code, which is the
entire reason you call MIT and BSD licenses Cuck Licenses.

Basically, it seems as though you are correct when it comes to licensing
programs themselves. But it gets murkier when talking about libraries.

[other personal details omitted]
</code></pre>
</blockquote>
<p>This was my response to this email explaining this finer point.</p>
<blockquote>
<pre><code>Yeah. There are sometimes times when it is tactically better to license
things under a permissive license if for institutional reasons:
mass-adoption is required and companies and such might be unnerved by
the GPL. Libraries might often be like that. So it's not necessarily a
purity-spiralling point.

RMS actually advised that ogg/vorbis should use a cuck license to
maximize adoption (it originally used the LGPL, but switched to BSD):

https://lwn.net/2001/0301/a/rms-ov-license.php3

It's thanks to this that it has now become a usable and wide-spread
format, used now on nearly every proprietary web service because of its
small-size, good fidelity and general superiority.

So yeah, if you're writing a standalone program, I'd use the GPL, but I
would choose licenses ultimately in terms of which would maximize the
possibilities for users of using free-software. In some circumstances,
that means using a cuck license. Same is true of the LGPL. I think
GNU/FSF recommend LGPL only to be used when it is competing with a
proprietary library, and if that's usually what you are writing, you
might end up writing a lot in the LGPL.
</code></pre>
</blockquote>]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-11 00:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/why-i-use-the-gpl-and-not-cuck-licenses/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/why-i-use-the-gpl-and-not-cuck-licenses/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[‘No one’s safe under these laws’: Surveillance Bill could target activists and downloaders]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-10 13:10:45+00:00</pubDate><link>https://thenewdaily.com.au/life/tech/2020/12/10/dutton-surveillance-bill-australia/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://thenewdaily.com.au/life/tech/2020/12/10/dutton-surveillance-bill-australia/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Sci-fi surveillance: Europe's secretive push into biometric technology]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>EU science funding is being spent on developing new tools for policing and security. But who decides how far we need to submit to artificial intelligence?</p><p>Patrick Breyer didn’t expect to have to take the European commission to court. The softly spoken German MEP was startled when in July 2019 he read about a new technology to detect from facial “micro-expressions” when somebody is lying while answering questions.</p><p>Even more startling was that the EU was funding research into this virtual mindreader through a project called iBorderCtrl, for potential use in policing Europe’s borders. In the <a href="https://theintercept.com/2019/07/26/europe-border-control-ai-lie-detector/">article</a> that Breyer read, a reporter described taking a test on the border between Serbia and Hungary. She told the truth, but the AI border guard said she had lied.</p> <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/dec/10/sci-fi-surveillance-europes-secretive-push-into-biometric-technology">Continue reading...</a>]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-10 13:00:02+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/dec/10/sci-fi-surveillance-europes-secretive-push-into-biometric-technology</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/dec/10/sci-fi-surveillance-europes-secretive-push-into-biometric-technology</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Facebook hit with antitrust lawsuit from FTC and 48 state attorneys general - ABC News]]</title><description>![CDATA[Facebook hit with antitrust lawsuit from FTC and 48 state attorneys general - ABC News]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-09 19:21:03+00:00</pubDate><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/facebook-hit-antitrust-lawsuit-ftc-48-state-attorneys/story?id=74623634</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://abcnews.go.com/Business/facebook-hit-antitrust-lawsuit-ftc-48-state-attorneys/story?id=74623634</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[What psychology can tell us about why some people don’t wear masks – and how to change their minds]]</title><description>![CDATA[What psychology can tell us about why some people don’t wear masks – and how to change their minds]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-09 10:01:53+00:00</pubDate><link>https://theconversation.com/what-psychology-can-tell-us-about-why-some-people-dont-wear-masks-and-how-to-change-their-minds-150343</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://theconversation.com/what-psychology-can-tell-us-about-why-some-people-dont-wear-masks-and-how-to-change-their-minds-150343</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[SoCal restaurant owners defy orders to close despite regional stay-at-home order - ABC7 Los Angeles]]</title><description>![CDATA[SoCal restaurant owners defy orders to close despite regional stay-at-home order - ABC7 Los Angeles]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-08 20:06:28+00:00</pubDate><link>https://abc7.com/california-coronavirus-socal-lockdown-stay-at-home-order-gov-gavin-newsom/8595340/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://abc7.com/california-coronavirus-socal-lockdown-stay-at-home-order-gov-gavin-newsom/8595340/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The American Companies Enabling China’s Uyghur Genocide]]</title><description>![CDATA[The American Companies Enabling China’s Uyghur Genocide]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-04 12:32:25+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theamericanconservative.com/the-american-companies-enabling-chinas-uyghur-genocide/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theamericanconservative.com/the-american-companies-enabling-chinas-uyghur-genocide/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[A green wave of ESG is poised to break over China]]</title><description>![CDATA[A green wave of ESG is poised to break over China]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-04 08:11:34+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2020/12/green-wave-of-esg-investment-is-breaking-in-china/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2020/12/green-wave-of-esg-investment-is-breaking-in-china/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Who Is Brian Deese? Biden Taps Former Obama Climate Aide : Biden Transition Updates : NPR]]</title><description>![CDATA[Who Is Brian Deese? Biden Taps Former Obama Climate Aide : Biden Transition Updates : NPR]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-03 22:48:15+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/biden-transition-updates/2020/12/03/942205555/biden-names-blackrocks-brian-deese-as-his-top-economic-aide</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/biden-transition-updates/2020/12/03/942205555/biden-names-blackrocks-brian-deese-as-his-top-economic-aide</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Eton was right to sack teacher Will Knowland]]</title><description>![CDATA[Eton was right to sack teacher Will Knowland]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-03 20:33:35+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.spectator.co.uk/article/eton-was-right-to-sack-will-knowland/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.spectator.co.uk/article/eton-was-right-to-sack-will-knowland/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[California plans sweeping stay-at-home order as Covid cases surge | California | The Guardian]]</title><description>![CDATA[California plans sweeping stay-at-home order as Covid cases surge | California | The Guardian]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-03 20:01:46+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/dec/03/california-covid-restrictions-stay-at-home-order</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/dec/03/california-covid-restrictions-stay-at-home-order</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Journalists across EU face wave of attacks covering anti-lockdown protests]]</title><description>![CDATA[Journalists across EU face wave of attacks covering anti-lockdown protests]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-03 10:13:24+00:00</pubDate><link>https://ipi.media/journalists-across-eu-face-wave-of-attacks-covering-anti-lockdown-protests/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ipi.media/journalists-across-eu-face-wave-of-attacks-covering-anti-lockdown-protests/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Coronavirus vaccine: Pfizer given protection from legal action by UK government]]</title><description>![CDATA[Coronavirus vaccine: Pfizer given protection from legal action by UK government]]</description><pubDate>2020-12-02 22:05:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/coronavirus-pfizer-vaccine-legal-indemnity-safety-ministers-b1765124.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/coronavirus-pfizer-vaccine-legal-indemnity-safety-ministers-b1765124.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Corona’s orchestra of panic: How the press’ fear-mongering is distorting information | European Journalism Observatory - EJO]]</title><description>![CDATA[Corona’s orchestra of panic: How the press’ fear-mongering is distorting information | European Journalism Observatory - EJO]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-30 11:34:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://en.ejo.ch/specialist-journalism/coronas-orchestra-of-panic-how-the-press-fear-mongering-is-distorting-information-about-covid-19</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.ejo.ch/specialist-journalism/coronas-orchestra-of-panic-how-the-press-fear-mongering-is-distorting-information-about-covid-19</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Time's Up charities set up by celebrities as part of Me Too movement spent $1.4m on salaries including $157k on conferences at luxury resorts]]</title><description>![CDATA[Time's Up charities set up by celebrities as part of Me Too movement spent $1.4m on salaries including $157k on conferences at luxury resorts]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-29 20:26:43+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8997707/Times-organization-raised-3-6m-2018-cash-went-salaries-not-victims.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8997707/Times-organization-raised-3-6m-2018-cash-went-salaries-not-victims.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[In Japan, more people died from suicide last month than from Covid in all of 2020 | CNN]]</title><description>![CDATA[In Japan, more people died from suicide last month than from Covid in all of 2020 | CNN]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-29 19:49:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/11/28/asia/japan-suicide-women-covid-dst-intl-hnk/index.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://edition.cnn.com/2020/11/28/asia/japan-suicide-women-covid-dst-intl-hnk/index.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Car Tires Are a Major Pollution Problem - The Atlantic]]</title><description>![CDATA[Car Tires Are a Major Pollution Problem - The Atlantic]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-29 11:27:42+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/11/car-tires-pollution-microplastic/617216/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/11/car-tires-pollution-microplastic/617216/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Star-studded Time’s Up charities spent big on salaries, little on helping victims]]</title><description>![CDATA[Star-studded Time’s Up charities spent big on salaries, little on helping victims]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-28 20:25:51+00:00</pubDate><link>https://nypost.com/2020/11/28/star-studded-times-up-charities-spent-big-on-salaries-not-victims/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://nypost.com/2020/11/28/star-studded-times-up-charities-spent-big-on-salaries-not-victims/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[WikiLeaks 'Cablegate' 10 years on]]</title><description>![CDATA[WikiLeaks 'Cablegate' 10 years on]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-28 20:05:21+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dw.com/en/wikileaks-cablegate-10-years-on-an-unvarnished-look-at-us-foreign-policy/a-55755239</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dw.com/en/wikileaks-cablegate-10-years-on-an-unvarnished-look-at-us-foreign-policy/a-55755239</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[New Jersey Starbucks barista claims she was fired for refusing to wear a Pride T-shirt because of her religious beliefs]]</title><description>![CDATA[New Jersey Starbucks barista claims she was fired for refusing to wear a Pride T-shirt because of her religious beliefs]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-27 22:05:08+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8993007/New-Jersey-Starbucks-barista-claims-fired-refusing-wear-Pride-T-shirt.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8993007/New-Jersey-Starbucks-barista-claims-fired-refusing-wear-Pride-T-shirt.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[You Own Nothing: The True Cost of Digital Media]]</title><description>![CDATA[You Own Nothing: The True Cost of Digital Media]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-27 20:54:09+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iSGu_P185s4</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iSGu_P185s4</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[How Does China's Social Credit System Work?]]</title><description>![CDATA[How Does China's Social Credit System Work?]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-26 21:00:47+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PVkWokLqPOg</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PVkWokLqPOg</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Microsoft productivity score feature criticised as workplace surveillance | Microsoft | The Guardian]]</title><description>![CDATA[Microsoft productivity score feature criticised as workplace surveillance | Microsoft | The Guardian]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-26 08:49:28+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/nov/26/microsoft-productivity-score-feature-criticised-workplace-surveillance</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/nov/26/microsoft-productivity-score-feature-criticised-workplace-surveillance</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA["A grave mistake", Kenney apologizes for lockdown]]</title><description>![CDATA["A grave mistake", Kenney apologizes for lockdown]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-25 08:43:31+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ylTCTcSM09Y</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ylTCTcSM09Y</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[AstraZeneca must prove it won't profit from COVID-19 vaccine - MSF | Reuters]]</title><description>![CDATA[AstraZeneca must prove it won't profit from COVID-19 vaccine - MSF | Reuters]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-24 21:56:21+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-health-coronavirus-astrazeneca-contra-idUKKBN2841FA</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-health-coronavirus-astrazeneca-contra-idUKKBN2841FA</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Google’s Cash Makes Rivals Less Eager for Antitrust Crackdown]]</title><description>![CDATA[Google’s Cash Makes Rivals Less Eager for Antitrust Crackdown]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-24 19:57:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-11-24/deals-with-apple-aapl-mozilla-show-how-google-googl-discourages-competition</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-11-24/deals-with-apple-aapl-mozilla-show-how-google-googl-discourages-competition</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[13 law enforcement agencies that refuse to enforce California’s new curfew and why – Investment Watch]]</title><description>![CDATA[13 law enforcement agencies that refuse to enforce California’s new curfew and why – Investment Watch]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-23 20:04:36+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.investmentwatchblog.com/13-law-enforcement-agencies-that-refuse-to-enforce-californias-new-curfew-and-why/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.investmentwatchblog.com/13-law-enforcement-agencies-that-refuse-to-enforce-californias-new-curfew-and-why/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Post-lockdown SARS-CoV-2 nucleic acid screening in nearly ten million residents of Wuhan, China]]</title><description>![CDATA[Post-lockdown SARS-CoV-2 nucleic acid screening in nearly ten million residents of Wuhan, China]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-20 11:39:07+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-020-19802-w</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-020-19802-w</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Danish study finds face masks provide limited protection to wearer | Reuters]]</title><description>![CDATA[Danish study finds face masks provide limited protection to wearer | Reuters]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-18 19:57:37+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-facemasks-idUSKBN27Y1YW</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-facemasks-idUSKBN27Y1YW</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Does Apple Track Every Mac App You Run? OCSP Explained]]</title><description>![CDATA[Does Apple Track Every Mac App You Run? OCSP Explained]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-18 15:23:40+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.howtogeek.com/701176/does-apple-track-every-mac-app-you-run-ocsp-explained/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.howtogeek.com/701176/does-apple-track-every-mac-app-you-run-ocsp-explained/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Why Smart Cities Threaten Citizens’ Right to Privacy]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-18 12:04:50+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.urbanet.info/why-smart-city-data-treatens-citizens-right-to-privacy/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.urbanet.info/why-smart-city-data-treatens-citizens-right-to-privacy/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Turn Off Gmail's 'Smart' Features to Avoid Tracking]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-17 12:04:49+00:00</pubDate><link>https://lifehacker.com/turn-off-gmails-smart-features-to-avoid-tracking-1845691806</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lifehacker.com/turn-off-gmails-smart-features-to-avoid-tracking-1845691806</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Mac certificate check stokes fears that Apple logs every app you run]]</title><description>![CDATA[Mac certificate check stokes fears that Apple logs every app you run]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-16 20:12:04+00:00</pubDate><link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2020/11/mac-certificate-check-stokes-fears-apple-logs-every-app-you-run/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2020/11/mac-certificate-check-stokes-fears-apple-logs-every-app-you-run/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[New lawsuit: Why do Android phones mysteriously exchange 260MB a month with Google via cellular data when they're not even in use?]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-14 12:04:50+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theregister.com/2020/11/14/google_android_data_allowance/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theregister.com/2020/11/14/google_android_data_allowance/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Are Babies Really Being Sold to Gay Couples in a Brussels Child Fair?]]</title><description>![CDATA[Are Babies Really Being Sold to Gay Couples in a Brussels Child Fair?]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-12 08:45:01+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.albawaba.com/node/are-babies-really-being-sold-gay-couples-brussels-child-fair-1392439</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.albawaba.com/node/are-babies-really-being-sold-gay-couples-brussels-child-fair-1392439</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Norway outlaws hate speech against trans people]]</title><description>![CDATA[Norway outlaws hate speech against trans people]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-10 22:01:46+00:00</pubDate><link>https://news.trust.org/item/20201110191107-tecjt/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.trust.org/item/20201110191107-tecjt/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Netherlands uncovers network helping Ugandan asylum seekers fake being gay]]</title><description>![CDATA[Netherlands uncovers network helping Ugandan asylum seekers fake being gay]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-05 21:05:40+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-netherlands-lgbt-asylum-trfn-idUSKBN27L29M</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reuters.com/article/us-netherlands-lgbt-asylum-trfn-idUSKBN27L29M</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Deconstructing the Lebanese central bank’s Ponzi scheme | The Economist]]</title><description>![CDATA[Deconstructing the Lebanese central bank’s Ponzi scheme | The Economist]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-05 20:45:57+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2020/11/05/deconstructing-the-lebanese-central-banks-ponzi-scheme</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2020/11/05/deconstructing-the-lebanese-central-banks-ponzi-scheme</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Twitter censors Trump’s tweets about ‘disappearing’ ballots]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-11-04 06:58:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://nypost.com/2020/11/04/twitter-censors-trumps-tweets-about-disappearing-ballots/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://nypost.com/2020/11/04/twitter-censors-trumps-tweets-about-disappearing-ballots/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Epstein donations force resignation at international peace organization]]</title><description>![CDATA[The president of an international think tank has resigned following revelations that he accepted a loan from accused sex trafficker Jeffrey Epstein and secured $650,000 in donations from foundations linked to Epstein for the peace organization.]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-31 00:39:16+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/10/30/world/epstein-donations-international-peace-institute-resign/index.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cnn.com/2020/10/30/world/epstein-donations-international-peace-institute-resign/index.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Amazon third-quarter earnings soar as pandemic sales triple profits | Amazon | The Guardian]]</title><description>![CDATA[Amazon third-quarter earnings soar as pandemic sales triple profits | Amazon | The Guardian]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-29 21:51:16+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/oct/29/amazon-profits-latest-earnings-report-third-quarter-pandemic</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/oct/29/amazon-profits-latest-earnings-report-third-quarter-pandemic</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The Heinous Background of WHO Director-General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus]]</title><description>![CDATA[The Heinous Background of WHO Director-General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-23 18:41:12+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.rodefshalom613.org/2020/10/the-heinous-background-of-who-director-general-tedros-adhanom-ghebreyesus/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rodefshalom613.org/2020/10/the-heinous-background-of-who-director-general-tedros-adhanom-ghebreyesus/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Google Paid Apple Billions To Dominate Search On iPhones, Justice Department Says : NPR]]</title><description>![CDATA[Google Paid Apple Billions To Dominate Search On iPhones, Justice Department Says : NPR]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-22 16:32:28+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.npr.org/2020/10/22/926290942/google-paid-apple-billions-to-dominate-search-on-iphones-justice-department-says</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/10/22/926290942/google-paid-apple-billions-to-dominate-search-on-iphones-justice-department-says</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The DOJ Just Slammed Google With a Landmark Antitrust Case | Entrepreneur]]</title><description>![CDATA[The DOJ Just Slammed Google With a Landmark Antitrust Case | Entrepreneur]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-20 11:15:42+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.entrepreneur.com/business-news/the-doj-just-slammed-google-with-a-landmark-antitrust-case/358109</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.entrepreneur.com/business-news/the-doj-just-slammed-google-with-a-landmark-antitrust-case/358109</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Facebook, Twitter employees send over 90% of political donations to Democrats: report | Fox News]]</title><description>![CDATA[Facebook, Twitter employees send over 90% of political donations to Democrats: report | Fox News]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-16 19:47:48+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/facebook-twitter-employees-donations-democrats</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/facebook-twitter-employees-donations-democrats</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Facebook to ban ads discouraging vaccination]]</title><description>![CDATA[Facebook to ban ads discouraging vaccination]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-13 13:18:42+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/oct/13/facebook-vaccine-ads-ban</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/oct/13/facebook-vaccine-ads-ban</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[WHO official urges world leaders to stop using lockdowns as primary virus control method | Washington Examiner]]</title><description>![CDATA[WHO official urges world leaders to stop using lockdowns as primary virus control method | Washington Examiner]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-10 19:51:18+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/who-official-urges-world-leaders-to-stop-using-lockdowns-as-primary-virus-control-method</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/who-official-urges-world-leaders-to-stop-using-lockdowns-as-primary-virus-control-method</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[EU's Digital Service Act will force makers to allow you to uninstall bloatware]]</title><description>![CDATA[EU's Digital Service Act will force makers to allow you to uninstall bloatware]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-10 18:35:47+00:00</pubDate><link>https://m.gsmarena.com/eus_digital_service_act_will_allow_you_to_uninstall_bloatware-news-45578.php</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://m.gsmarena.com/eus_digital_service_act_will_allow_you_to_uninstall_bloatware-news-45578.php</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[COVID-19 to Add as Many as 150 Million Extreme Poor by 2021]]</title><description>![CDATA[COVID-19 to Add as Many as 150 Million Extreme Poor by 2021]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-07 19:52:53+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.worldbank.org/en/news/press-release/2020/10/07/covid-19-to-add-as-many-as-150-million-extreme-poor-by-2021</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.worldbank.org/en/news/press-release/2020/10/07/covid-19-to-add-as-many-as-150-million-extreme-poor-by-2021</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[While the Poor Get Sick, Bill Gates Just Gets Richer | The Nation]]</title><description>![CDATA[While the Poor Get Sick, Bill Gates Just Gets Richer | The Nation]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-05 17:20:37+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.thenation.com/article/economy/bill-gates-investments-covid/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thenation.com/article/economy/bill-gates-investments-covid/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[A WeChat Ban Would End Their Lifeline - The New York Times]]</title><description>![CDATA[A WeChat Ban Would End Their Lifeline - The New York Times]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-05 16:16:09+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/10/05/nyregion/us-wechat-ban.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/10/05/nyregion/us-wechat-ban.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Dr Martin Feeley: I lost my job for speaking out]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-04 07:26:41+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.independent.ie/world-news/coronavirus/i-lost-my-job-for-speaking-out-but-i-have-no-regrets-dr-martin-feeley-on-his-coronavirus-views-39585808.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.independent.ie/world-news/coronavirus/i-lost-my-job-for-speaking-out-but-i-have-no-regrets-dr-martin-feeley-on-his-coronavirus-views-39585808.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Bipartisan bill would give Israel a veto on Middle East arms sales]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-03 12:50:43+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.jpost.com/american-politics/bipartisan-bill-would-give-israel-a-veto-on-middle-east-arms-sales-644326</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.jpost.com/american-politics/bipartisan-bill-would-give-israel-a-veto-on-middle-east-arms-sales-644326</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA['Woke utopia', the end of the West & a new cult - James Lindsay interview - BQ #33]]</title><description>![CDATA['Woke utopia', the end of the West & a new cult - James Lindsay interview - BQ #33]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-02 11:39:09+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dE8p-mcFdNg</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dE8p-mcFdNg</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Aldous Huxley - The Most Brutally Honest 8 Minutes Of Your Life!]]</title><description>![CDATA[Aldous Huxley - The Most Brutally Honest 8 Minutes Of Your Life!]]</description><pubDate>2020-10-01 21:01:54+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=67fm4D5Ii6E</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=67fm4D5Ii6E</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[French bar owners arrested for offering free WiFi but not keeping logs]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-30 13:08:38+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.privateinternetaccess.com/blog/french-bar-owners-arrested-for-offering-free-wifi-but-not-keeping-logs/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.privateinternetaccess.com/blog/french-bar-owners-arrested-for-offering-free-wifi-but-not-keeping-logs/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Louisiana man, 36, is arrested when Florida parents discover he has been living in their 15-year-old daughter's closet for more than a MONTH]]</title><description>![CDATA[Louisiana man, 36, is arrested when Florida parents discover he has been living in their 15-year-old daughter's closet for more than a MONTH]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-30 13:06:20+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8789849/Louisiana-man-living-15-year-old-Florida-girls-closet-MONTH.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8789849/Louisiana-man-living-15-year-old-Florida-girls-closet-MONTH.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Three million Uyghurs detained in concentration camps by Beijing: Activist - The Economic Times]]</title><description>![CDATA[Three million Uyghurs detained in concentration camps by Beijing: Activist - The Economic Times]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-27 20:56:51+00:00</pubDate><link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/three-million-uyghurs-detained-in-concentration-camps-by-beijing-activist/articleshow/78343963.cms</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/three-million-uyghurs-detained-in-concentration-camps-by-beijing-activist/articleshow/78343963.cms</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[BLM leader arrested for allegedly spending $200K in donations on tailored suits, a house, and guns | Washington Examiner]]</title><description>![CDATA[BLM leader arrested for allegedly spending $200K in donations on tailored suits, a house, and guns | Washington Examiner]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-27 19:17:54+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/blm-leader-arrested-for-allegedly-spending-200k-in-donations-on-tailored-suits-a-house-and-guns</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/blm-leader-arrested-for-allegedly-spending-200k-in-donations-on-tailored-suits-a-house-and-guns</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[On climate change, Exxon, BP, Shell, and other top oil companies have a long way to go - Vox]]</title><description>![CDATA[On climate change, Exxon, BP, Shell, and other top oil companies have a long way to go - Vox]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-25 12:49:31+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.vox.com/energy-and-environment/2020/9/25/21452055/climate-change-exxon-bp-shell-total-chevron-oil-gas</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.vox.com/energy-and-environment/2020/9/25/21452055/climate-change-exxon-bp-shell-total-chevron-oil-gas</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[BLM removes website language blasting 'nuclear family structure']]</title><description>![CDATA[BLM removes website language blasting 'nuclear family structure']]</description><pubDate>2020-09-24 21:02:02+00:00</pubDate><link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/24/blm-removes-website-language-blasting-nuclear-family-structure/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://nypost.com/2020/09/24/blm-removes-website-language-blasting-nuclear-family-structure/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Cold comfort: The sun is cooling; doesn't mean there'll be no global warming]]</title><description>![CDATA[Cold comfort: The sun is cooling; doesn't mean there'll be no global warming]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-23 14:32:51+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.downtoearth.org.in/news/science-technology/cold-comfort-the-sun-is-cooling-doesn-t-mean-there-ll-be-no-global-warming-73488</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.downtoearth.org.in/news/science-technology/cold-comfort-the-sun-is-cooling-doesn-t-mean-there-ll-be-no-global-warming-73488</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Carbon emissions of richest 1 percent more than double the emissions of the poorest half of humanity]]</title><description>![CDATA[Carbon emissions of richest 1 percent more than double the emissions of the poorest half of humanity]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-21 07:50:21+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.oxfam.org/en/press-releases/carbon-emissions-richest-1-percent-more-double-emissions-poorest-half-humanity</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.oxfam.org/en/press-releases/carbon-emissions-richest-1-percent-more-double-emissions-poorest-half-humanity</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Gates Foundation funds Facebook fact-checkers that defend it from allegations]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-21 07:17:36+00:00</pubDate><link>https://reclaimthenet.org/gates-foundation-funds-facebook-fact-checkers/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reclaimthenet.org/gates-foundation-funds-facebook-fact-checkers/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Myth as History: Rohl's New Chronology]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>In one fell swoop, Egyptologist David Rohl has posited a change in Egyptian chronology that takes both Greek mythical history and the stories of the Bible out of idle lore and into historical plausibility.</p><p>By cutting and rearranging some 300 years of "dark ages," Rohl suggests that there is no gap between the legendary times of the Trojan War and the later historical Dorian Invasion. He also posits that very specific Biblical stories, such as the sojourn in Egypt, Exodus, the conquest of Canaan and the Kingdom of Israel have ample historical evidence if we start looking in Egypt's Middle Kingdom Period.</p><p>Note also that you can now support <em>Not Related!</em> by donating at <a href="https://donate.notrelated.xyz">donate.notrelated.xyz</a>. Monthly pledges will only be charged at the start of the month if two episodes have been released in the previous month.</p><details>📚 See readings and other media.<p><em>Note that pay-walled academic articles may be obtained by feeding their URLs to sites like Sci-Hub.</em></p><ul><li><em>The Lords of Avaris</em> (David Rohl)</li><li><em>Exodus: Myth or History?</em> (David Rohl)</li><li><a href="https://patternsofevidence.com/"><em>Patterns of Evidence</em></a> (an Evangeliboomer apologetical documentary series on the Bible which in part features Rohl's revised chronology)</li></ul></details><h1>Timecodes</h1><pre>0:00:00	Introduction
0:00:45	Not Related! Is Back! (https://notrelated.xyz)
0:01:23	Rohl's New Chronology: Antidote to Mediocrity
0:03:46	The Boring Side of Chronology (Dating Pharaohs)
0:04:42	The History of the Historicity of Bible
0:06:19	The Story of Genesis in 30 Seconds
0:07:00	Genesis DEBOONKED? Traditional Chronology
0:08:56	Hebrew Israelites in the Middle Kangdom
0:10:43	Joseph's House
0:12:24	Bahr Yussef and the Sad Pharaohs
0:14:53	Evidence of Exodus and the Hyksos
0:16:46	Jericho
0:18:00	Biblical Minimalism and "Critical" Scholarship
0:23:03	Amarna Letters, Saul, David, Jonathan
0:25:35	Boomer Documentaries
0:27:44	No Risk Not Related! Funding (https://donate.notrelated.xyz)
0:29:42	Not Related! Size
0:30:35	Wittgenstein's TLP and Philosophical Investigations
0:31:30	t'Hooft as Chomsky and Amateur Spirit in Science
0:34:44	Graham Hancock and rigor
0:35:56	Marija Gimbutas and the Mother Goddess and Chalice and Blade
0:38:21	Soyence and "Skeptics"
0:39:55	Greek Mythology and the Trojan War
0:46:11	The Greek Dark Age and Greek Lineages
0:50:40	The Lords of Avaris, the Greeks and Hyksos
0:56:08	Greek Myth as Egyptian History
0:58:53	Cadmus, the Greek Alphabet and Hieroglyphs
1:04:47	Is the Aeneid just fan-fiction?
1:07:59	My personal assessment
1:12:15	What's to come in Not Related!</pre><h1>More...</h1><ul><li>The <em>Not Related!</em> website: <a href="https://notrelated.xyz"></a>notrelated.xyz</a></li><li>Donations will be read in the middle of each episode: <a href="https://donate.notrelated.xyz">donate.notrelated.xyz</a></li></ul>]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-21 04:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://notrelated.xyz/audio/s02/S02E03_-_Myth_as_History_Rohls_New_Chronology.ogg</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://notrelated.xyz/audio/s02/S02E03_-_Myth_as_History_Rohls_New_Chronology.ogg</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Open Letter from Medical Doctors and Health Professionals to All Belgian Authorities and All Belgian Media]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-20 06:39:30+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.aier.org/article/open-letter-from-medical-doctors-and-health-professionals-to-all-belgian-authorities-and-all-belgian-media/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.aier.org/article/open-letter-from-medical-doctors-and-health-professionals-to-all-belgian-authorities-and-all-belgian-media/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Trump Admin to Ban TikTok, WeChat From U.S. App Stores - The New York Times]]</title><description>![CDATA[Trump Admin to Ban TikTok, WeChat From U.S. App Stores - The New York Times]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-18 21:40:47+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/09/18/business/trump-tik-tok-wechat-ban.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/09/18/business/trump-tik-tok-wechat-ban.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Netflix Defends ‘Cuties’ as ‘Social Commentary’ Against Sexualization of Young Children]]</title><description>![CDATA[Netflix Defends ‘Cuties’ as ‘Social Commentary’ Against Sexualization of Young Children]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-10 08:25:33+00:00</pubDate><link>https://variety.com/2020/digital/news/netflix-defends-cuties-against-sexualization-young-girls-1234766347/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://variety.com/2020/digital/news/netflix-defends-cuties-against-sexualization-young-girls-1234766347/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Oscars' woke quota will backfire on Hollywood spectacularly]]</title><description>![CDATA[Oscars' woke quota will backfire on Hollywood spectacularly]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-09 14:51:17+00:00</pubDate><link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/09/oscars-woke-quota-will-backfire-on-hollywood-spectacularly/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://nypost.com/2020/09/09/oscars-woke-quota-will-backfire-on-hollywood-spectacularly/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Rak jest groźniejszy niż koronawirus!]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-09 07:24:46+00:00</pubDate><link>https://wco.pl/2020/09/09/rak-jest-grozniejszy-niz-koronawirus/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://wco.pl/2020/09/09/rak-jest-grozniejszy-niz-koronawirus/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Norway will prioritise lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender refugees]]</title><description>![CDATA[Norway will prioritise lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender refugees]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-07 21:01:23+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.euronews.com/2020/07/09/norway-will-prioritise-lesbian-gay-bisexual-and-transgender-refugees</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.euronews.com/2020/07/09/norway-will-prioritise-lesbian-gay-bisexual-and-transgender-refugees</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Forget TikTok. China’s Powerhouse App Is WeChat. - The New York Times]]</title><description>![CDATA[Forget TikTok. China’s Powerhouse App Is WeChat. - The New York Times]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-04 16:12:51+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/09/04/technology/wechat-china-united-states.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/09/04/technology/wechat-china-united-states.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Portland's grim reality: 100 days of protests, many violent | AP News]]</title><description>![CDATA[Portland's grim reality: 100 days of protests, many violent | AP News]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-04 14:30:38+00:00</pubDate><link>https://apnews.com/article/virus-outbreak-ap-top-news-race-and-ethnicity-id-state-wire-or-state-wire-b57315d97dd2146c4a89b4636faa7b70</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://apnews.com/article/virus-outbreak-ap-top-news-race-and-ethnicity-id-state-wire-or-state-wire-b57315d97dd2146c4a89b4636faa7b70</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Hedonism, Asceticism and the Hermetic Answer]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>The modern world more or less gives you the philosophical choice of
either <em>Hedonism</em> or <em>Asceticism</em>. You never really hear it
in those terms, but that's how it is.</p>
<p><strong>Hedonism living for pleasure.</strong> Your default lifestyle is eating
whatever, watching Netflix and playing video games irrespective of how
late it is. You watch porn, masturbate, have sex as much as you can and
any consequences of any of this are just facts of life which you view as
either out of your control or worth the suffering. You might not use
drugs because you are worried of the hedonistic damage it can cause, but
you're at least &ldquo;chill&rdquo; with people who do. At a basic level, modern
society is hedonistic because it more or less openly holds as highest
moral value what can stimulate people the most. You know this is the
case because anyone who <em>condemns</em> hedonistic behavior will immediately
be judged as &ldquo;judgemental.&rdquo;</p>
<p><strong>Asceticism is supposed to be the &ldquo;smart&rdquo; alternative.</strong> Asceticism is
rejecting pleasure, normal life and anything else enjoyable in the world
as morally inferior to some higher non-physical ideal. Buddhism, which
rejects the physical world, has become a popular meme philosophy in the
West and is highly acetic. Vegans are acetic: they abandon basic life
for their own principles and intense vegans will eventually start
talking about &quot;transcending&quot; and &quot;vibrations&quot; and non-sense. Look at
the anti-global warming movements and they fall perfectly, almost
neurotically into this category. Asceticism come in many forms nowadays,
but it is always a reaction to the indulgences of hedonism.</p>
<h2 id="the-poetic-worldview">The Poetic Worldview</h2>
<p><a href="https://renaissanceastrology.com/hermestrismegistus.html"></a></p>

<figure class="resright"><img src="https://lukesmith.xyz/pix/hermes.png" /><figcaption>Hermes Trismegistus, author of the Hermetic Corpus</figcaption></figure>

<p>The Poetic Worldview is the solution. Don't worry, it has nothing to do
with poetry.</p>
<p>The Greek word that <em>poetry/poetic</em> comes from actually is just a
generic word for <em>make, create, produce</em>. The word &quot;poetry&quot; originally
just meant something like &quot;creative output.&quot;</p>
<p>This view is tied into early Platonism and monotheism. The physical
universe is a creation or manifestation or &quot;the One&quot; or &quot;the Source&quot;
or really [God]{.dfn}. God is the ultimate creator, and an individual is
<strong>good</strong> insofar as [he reflects this creative tendency of God]{.dfn}.
We see it expounded in the Hermetic Corpus:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&ldquo;The other name of God is Father, again because He is the
that-which-maketh-all. The part of father is to make.&rdquo; <a href="http://www.gnosis.org/library/grs-mead/TGH-v2/th205.html">To
Asclepius</a>
(17), from the <a href="http://www.gnosis.org/library/hermet.htm">Hermetic
Corpus</a></p>
</blockquote>
<p>In the Poetic Worldview, <strong>the highest moral goal is creation</strong>. That
can be:</p>
<ul>
<li>affecting the world,</li>
<li>improving what is around you,</li>
<li>having children,</li>
<li>making money not to spend it on pleasures, but to make something new
and great with it,</li>
<li>writing or making something useful or edifying for others,</li>
<li>clearing up misconceptions that get in other people's way in
accomplishing these things.</li>
</ul>
<p>From the Poetic worldview, hedonism is evil because it is expending
otherwise creative energy into nothing of consequence. Racking up
video-game achievements that no one will ever know or care of but you,
watching pornography, pursuing fleeting relationships, impulsively
wasting time browsing the internet and fiddling with social media.</p>
<p>This passive and impulsive pleasure-seeking reduces someone's ability
to live as intended, instead, they are prisoners to their lusts and
conveniences:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&ldquo;But whatsoever human souls have not the Mind as pilot, they share in
the same fate as souls of lives irrational. For [Mind] becomes
co-worker with them, giving full play to the desires towards which
[such souls] are borne,&mdash;[desires] that from the rush of lust
strain after the irrational; [so that such human souls,] just like
irrational animals, cease not irrationally to rage and lust, nor ever
are they satiate of ills. For passions and irrational desires are ills
exceeding great; and over these God hath set up the Mind to play the
part of judge and executioner.&rdquo; <a href="http://www.gnosis.org/library/grs-mead/TGH-v2/th225.html">About the Common
Mind</a> (4),
from the <a href="http://www.gnosis.org/library/hermet.htm">Hermetic Corpus</a></p>
</blockquote>
<p>Hedonism is additionally harmful because <em>it isn't even hedonistic</em>.
It's clumsy and self-destructive. Spend your life from ages 16-23
playing videogames, masturbating and smoking weed and you have destroyed
your capacity to enjoy life, sex and have normal interactions with
normal people. Your capacity for enjoyment ends and you fall into
asceticism as a cope.</p>
<p><strong>Asceticism is just as evil</strong> because it sees this issue with the
hedonistic lifestyle and tosses up its hands in surrender. It
internalizes the lie that wasteful and sinful living is somehow
obviously funner&mdash;when they see they aren't actually having fun, they
throw the whole world away.</p>
<p><strong>Most ascetics are liars anyway.</strong> They pretend to reject pleasure and
worldly things, but they often just seek it in perverted or
unconventional ways. There are men who call themselves MGTOW (Men going
their own way) who &quot;swear off&quot; women. In reality, most of them are
just desperate porn-addicted men who just can't get the girl they want.</p>
<p>Contrary to all of this, having a Poetic view proposes that the more
moral and also most enjoyable life is one where one is constantly
creating something new out of what he is given. In Hermetic thinking
(and, well, Christian thinking) man must hold God as the idea to
emulate. Since God's principle feat is creation from nothing, our goal
is to celebrate that creation by making something new and productive
from the raw materials we have.</p>
<p>Asceticism views the material world <em>as a mistake or illusion</em> which
leads people to reject life itself. The Poetic view is that the physical
world is a <strong>reflection of its spiritual state</strong>, and what you do in the
physical world reflects your spiritual stature.</p>
<p>The Poetic view is <em>somewhat</em> similar to Nietzsche's <em>Will to Power</em>,
which was an attempt to unite both human and material
sciences under the idea that the ideal is maximizing one's output on
the external world. Will to Power is a little more morally ambivalent
though; it can include destruction, while Poeticism merely values
creative power.</p>
<h2 id="distractions-are-literally-evil">Distractions are literally evil.</h2>
<p>This is why <em>I highly condemn wasteful activities like videogames and pornography and social media.</em> They are principally habits that
divert your natural energies into something absolutely sterile. <strong>Many
people ask me &ldquo;What can I do to be more productive?&rdquo;</strong> and I have to say
that the most important thing is to <strong>remove inert distractions and
habits</strong>.</p>
<p>Due to bureaucratic workplaces and bureaucratic education, there are
many modern people who <em>just don't know what it means to be
productive</em>. Most of their lives might be someone trying to fill their
day with busywork. Since the normal enjoyable ritual of creative output
is unknown to them, this causes a kind of aimlessness and the <a href="https://lukesmith.xyz/files/unabomber.pdf">feelings
of inferiority</a> that comes with that.</p>
<p>But in truth, you live at <strong>an ideal period</strong> in that you can have a
highly impactful and ergo <em>poetic</em> effect on the world using internet
technology and the higher material standard of living. The only trick is
to sidestep the distractions of hedonism that turns you into a passive
consumer and the apathy of asceticism.</p>]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-03 00:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/hedonism-asceticism-and-the-hermetic-answer/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/hedonism-asceticism-and-the-hermetic-answer/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[California Acts to Increase LGBT, Racial Diversity on Corporate Boards]]</title><description>![CDATA[California Acts to Increase LGBT, Racial Diversity on Corporate Boards]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-02 21:12:40+00:00</pubDate><link>https://southfloridagaynews.com/National/california-acts-to-increase-lgbt-racial-diversity-on-corporate-boards.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://southfloridagaynews.com/National/california-acts-to-increase-lgbt-racial-diversity-on-corporate-boards.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Academics Are Really, Really Worried About Their Freedom]]</title><description>![CDATA[Academics Are Really, Really Worried About Their Freedom]]</description><pubDate>2020-09-01 22:02:49+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/09/academics-are-really-really-worried-about-their-freedom/615724/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/09/academics-are-really-really-worried-about-their-freedom/615724/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Google Meet, Microsoft Teams, Webex Privacy Issues - Consumer Reports]]</title><description>![CDATA[Google Meet, Microsoft Teams, Webex Privacy Issues - Consumer Reports]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-30 08:50:38+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.consumerreports.org/video-conferencing-services/videoconferencing-privacy-issues-google-microsoft-webex-a7383469308/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.consumerreports.org/video-conferencing-services/videoconferencing-privacy-issues-google-microsoft-webex-a7383469308/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The huge change coming to how you claim government benefits: Aussies will use new $250million facial recognition to access services]]</title><description>![CDATA[test]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-29 20:08:11+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8783517/Australian-government-introduces-250million-facial-recognition-access-Centrelink-benefits-dole.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8783517/Australian-government-introduces-250million-facial-recognition-access-Centrelink-benefits-dole.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Coronavirus sceptics, conspiracy theorists and anti-vaxxers protest in London]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>Thousands gather in Trafalgar Square to hear calls for lockdown rules to be removed</p><ul><li><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/series/coronavirus-live/latest">Coronavirus – latest updates</a></li><li><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/coronavirus-outbreak">See all our coronavirus coverage</a></li></ul><p>Thousands of protesters from across the UK gathered in London’s Trafalgar Square on Saturday afternoon to protest against coronavirus restrictions and reject mass vaccinations.</p><p>The event, which began at noon, drew a broad coalition including coronavirus sceptics, 5G conspiracy theorists and so-called “anti-vaxxers”.</p> <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/29/coronavirus-sceptics-conspiracy-theorists-anti-vaxxers-protest-london">Continue reading...</a>]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-29 15:12:08+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/29/coronavirus-sceptics-conspiracy-theorists-anti-vaxxers-protest-london</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/29/coronavirus-sceptics-conspiracy-theorists-anti-vaxxers-protest-london</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The Social Dilemma | Official Trailer | NetflixThe Social Dilemma | Official Trailer | Netflix]]</title><description>![CDATA[The Social Dilemma | Official Trailer | Netflix]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-27 08:41:27+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uaaC57tcci0</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uaaC57tcci0</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Google stifles growing YouTube competitor LBRY by banning it from Play Store for pedantic reasons]]</title><description>![CDATA[Google stifles growing YouTube competitor LBRY by banning it from Play Store for pedantic reasons]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-25 20:07:21+00:00</pubDate><link>https://reclaimthenet.org/google-bans-lbry/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://reclaimthenet.org/google-bans-lbry/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Unredacted suit shows Google’s own engineers confused by privacy settings]]</title><description>![CDATA[Unredacted suit shows Google’s own engineers confused by privacy settings]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-25 20:06:39+00:00</pubDate><link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/08/unredacted-suit-shows-googles-own-engineers-confused-by-privacy-settings/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/08/unredacted-suit-shows-googles-own-engineers-confused-by-privacy-settings/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[COVID-19 lab leak theory]]</title><description>![CDATA[COVID-19 lab leak theory]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-25 06:52:20+00:00</pubDate><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/COVID-19_lab_leak_theory</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/COVID-19_lab_leak_theory</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Enough with the Linux security FUD]]</title><description>![CDATA[Enough with the Linux security FUD]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-24 13:58:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/enough-with-the-linux-security-fud/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.zdnet.com/article/enough-with-the-linux-security-fud/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[US tells Kenya to publicly support Israel or forget free trade deal]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-21 12:51:44+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theeastafrican.co.ke/tea/news/east-africa/us-tells-kenya-to-support-israel-or-forget-free-trade-deal-2304192</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theeastafrican.co.ke/tea/news/east-africa/us-tells-kenya-to-support-israel-or-forget-free-trade-deal-2304192</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[US coronavirus deaths could top 6,000 a day by December in worst-case scenario, expert predicts]]</title><description>![CDATA[US coronavirus deaths could top 6,000 a day by December in worst-case scenario, expert predicts]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-21 11:39:16+00:00</pubDate><link>https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-21-20-intl#h_e869402891201d42d0937c0fe789a1df</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-21-20-intl#h_e869402891201d42d0937c0fe789a1df</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Goodyear employees say new zero-tolerance policy from Akron HQ is discriminatory]]</title><description>![CDATA[Goodyear employees say new zero-tolerance policy from Akron HQ is discriminatory]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-19 21:11:08+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cleveland19.com/2020/08/18/goodyear-employees-say-new-zero-tolerance-policy-akron-hq-is-discriminatory/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cleveland19.com/2020/08/18/goodyear-employees-say-new-zero-tolerance-policy-akron-hq-is-discriminatory/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[New P2P botnet infects SSH servers all over the world]]</title><description>![CDATA[New P2P botnet infects SSH servers all over the world]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-19 20:04:48+00:00</pubDate><link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2020/08/new-p2p-botnet-infects-ssh-servers-all-over-the-world/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2020/08/new-p2p-botnet-infects-ssh-servers-all-over-the-world/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Protesters burn government building during riot in Portland]]</title><description>![CDATA[Protesters burn government building during riot in Portland]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-19 14:32:19+00:00</pubDate><link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/19/protesters-burn-government-building-during-riot-in-portland/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://nypost.com/2020/08/19/protesters-burn-government-building-during-riot-in-portland/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Write Code as If You Had to Support It for the Rest of Your Life]]</title><description>![CDATA[Write Code as If You Had to Support It for the Rest of Your Life]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-17 09:59:59+00:00</pubDate><link>https://medium.com/oreillymedia/write-code-as-if-you-had-to-support-it-for-the-rest-of-your-life-a707d3442f1a</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/oreillymedia/write-code-as-if-you-had-to-support-it-for-the-rest-of-your-life-a707d3442f1a</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[BioNTech wins $445 million German grant for COVID-19 vaccine | Reuters]]</title><description>![CDATA[BioNTech wins $445 million German grant for COVID-19 vaccine | Reuters]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-15 21:59:40+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/health-coronavirus-germany-vaccine-idUSKBN2661KP</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reuters.com/article/health-coronavirus-germany-vaccine-idUSKBN2661KP</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Why is no one safe until everyone is safe during a pandemic? | Gavi, the Vaccine Alliance]]</title><description>![CDATA[Why is no one safe until everyone is safe during a pandemic? | Gavi, the Vaccine Alliance]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-14 22:07:07+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.gavi.org/vaccineswork/why-no-one-safe-until-everyone-safe-during-pandemic</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.gavi.org/vaccineswork/why-no-one-safe-until-everyone-safe-during-pandemic</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[NSA and FBI warn that new Linux malware threatens national security]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-13 06:48:38+00:00</pubDate><link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2020/08/nsa-and-fbi-warn-that-new-linux-malware-threatens-national-security/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2020/08/nsa-and-fbi-warn-that-new-linux-malware-threatens-national-security/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Why your 'Carbon Footprint' Is A Lie | Climate Town]]</title><description>![CDATA[Why your 'Carbon Footprint' Is A Lie | Climate Town]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-12 07:47:34+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1J9LOqiXdpE</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1J9LOqiXdpE</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[400+ Qualcomm Chip Vulnerabilities Threaten Millions of Android Phones]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-07 06:43:11+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities---threats/400+-qualcomm-chip-vulnerabilities-threaten-millions-of-android-phones/d/d-id/1338613</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities---threats/400+-qualcomm-chip-vulnerabilities-threaten-millions-of-android-phones/d/d-id/1338613</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Massive 20GB Intel IP Data Breach Floods the Internet, Mentions Backdoors (Intel Responds)]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-06 06:47:11+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/massive-20gb-intel-data-breach-floods-the-internet-mentions-backdoors</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.tomshardware.com/news/massive-20gb-intel-data-breach-floods-the-internet-mentions-backdoors</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Transgender row teacher 'sacked' from second school]]</title><description>![CDATA[Transgender row teacher 'sacked' from second school]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-05 10:55:02+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-oxfordshire-53650010</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-oxfordshire-53650010</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[6 ways to improve your debugging skills]]</title><description>![CDATA[6 ways to improve your debugging skills]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-05 09:57:01+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.functionize.com/blog/6-ways-to-improve-your-debugging-skills/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.functionize.com/blog/6-ways-to-improve-your-debugging-skills/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Victoria Police arrest James Bartolo for online support of anti-lockdown protests]]</title><description>![CDATA[Victoria Police arrest James Bartolo for online support of anti-lockdown protests]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-04 21:08:09+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-09-04/victoria-police-arrest-fourth-person-for-supporting-protests/12630904</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-09-04/victoria-police-arrest-fourth-person-for-supporting-protests/12630904</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Beware of find-my-phone, Wi-Fi, and Bluetooth, NSA tells mobile users]]</title><description>![CDATA[Beware of find-my-phone, Wi-Fi, and Bluetooth, NSA tells mobile users]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-04 20:05:35+00:00</pubDate><link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/08/beware-of-find-my-phone-wi-fi-and-bluetooth-nsa-tells-mobile-users/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2020/08/beware-of-find-my-phone-wi-fi-and-bluetooth-nsa-tells-mobile-users/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Google Home might be listening to more than just wake words after secret update]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-08-04 12:04:50+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.techradar.com/news/google-home-might-be-listening-to-more-than-just-wake-words-after-secret-update</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.techradar.com/news/google-home-might-be-listening-to-more-than-just-wake-words-after-secret-update</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Stoicism and Christianity: Trust the Logos!]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p><em>The Word became flesh and dwelt among us.</em></p><p>Christian theology has a mostly dusty and forgotten belonging among the Pagan philosophy of the Greek east and the early Roman Empire. While Platonic, Hermetic and Gnostic thought all reinforced or butted heads with the Early Church, Stoic thought provides some of the most important vocabulary used in the Bible, particularly by John the Evangelist.</p><p>This viewpoint presents Jesus as not the incarnation of <em>Logos</em>, the rational order of the universe itself, but also as the Stoic ideal. The plan of Christ is to reunite man with God's order, in the same way that Stoics attempted to submit to divine <em>Logos</em>.</p><h1>More...</h1><ul><li>The <em>Not Related!</em> website: <a href="https://notrelated.xyz"></a>notrelated.xyz</a></li><li>Donations will be read in the middle of each episode: <a href="https://donate.notrelated.xyz">donate.notrelated.xyz</a></li></ul>]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-31 04:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://notrelated.xyz/audio/s02/S02E02_-_Stoicism_and_Christianity_Trust_the_Logos.ogg</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://notrelated.xyz/audio/s02/S02E02_-_Stoicism_and_Christianity_Trust_the_Logos.ogg</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[How George Soros broke the Bank of England | by Siddharth Singh | Zecide AI | Medium]]</title><description>![CDATA[How George Soros broke the Bank of England | by Siddharth Singh | Zecide AI | Medium]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-29 07:40:15+00:00</pubDate><link>https://medium.com/zecide-ai/how-george-soros-broke-the-bank-of-england-891611e9d8a6</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/zecide-ai/how-george-soros-broke-the-bank-of-england-891611e9d8a6</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Paedophile Labour councillor who worked in children's home walks free despite being caught with over one million child porn images including 12-year-old girls being raped]]</title><description>![CDATA[Paedophile Labour councillor who worked in children's home walks free despite being caught with over one million child porn images including 12-year-old girls being raped]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-28 21:09:04+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8568833/Paedophile-Labour-councillor-worked-childrens-home-walks-free.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8568833/Paedophile-Labour-councillor-worked-childrens-home-walks-free.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[INSANE: Netflix Pushes Trans Propaganda On KIDS Show; Shapiro Responds]]</title><description>![CDATA[INSANE: Netflix Pushes Trans Propaganda On KIDS Show; Shapiro Responds]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-27 09:07:25+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HxbOM6swuTg</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HxbOM6swuTg</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Moderna gets further $472 million U.S. award for coronavirus vaccine development | Reuters]]</title><description>![CDATA[Moderna gets further $472 million U.S. award for coronavirus vaccine development | Reuters]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-26 22:02:16+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-moderna-funding-idUSKCN24R0IN</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-moderna-funding-idUSKCN24R0IN</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Legal Docs: St. Louis Prosecutor Tampered With Evidence In McCloskey Gun Case]]</title><description>![CDATA[Legal Docs: St. Louis Prosecutor Tampered With Evidence In McCloskey Gun Case]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-23 08:17:09+00:00</pubDate><link>https://thefederalist.com/2020/07/23/legal-docs-st-louis-prosecutor-tampered-with-evidence-in-mccloskey-gun-case</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://thefederalist.com/2020/07/23/legal-docs-st-louis-prosecutor-tampered-with-evidence-in-mccloskey-gun-case</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[A $200 fine for not wearing a mask is fair, as long as free masks go to those in need]]</title><description>![CDATA[A $200 fine for not wearing a mask is fair, as long as free masks go to those in need]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-22 09:56:58+00:00</pubDate><link>https://theconversation.com/a-200-fine-for-not-wearing-a-mask-is-fair-as-long-as-free-masks-go-to-those-in-need-142988</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://theconversation.com/a-200-fine-for-not-wearing-a-mask-is-fair-as-long-as-free-masks-go-to-those-in-need-142988</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Shaming people who refuse to wear face masks isn’t a good look]]</title><description>![CDATA[Shaming people who refuse to wear face masks isn’t a good look]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-22 06:00:05+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2020/jul/22/shaming-people-who-refuse-to-wear-face-masks-isnt-a-good-look</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2020/jul/22/shaming-people-who-refuse-to-wear-face-masks-isnt-a-good-look</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Gunmen Kill 18 Wedding Guests in Northern Nigeria]]</title><description>![CDATA[Gunmen Kill 18 Wedding Guests in Northern Nigeria]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-21 21:04:07+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.thedefensepost.com/2020/07/21/gunmen-wedding-nigeria/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thedefensepost.com/2020/07/21/gunmen-wedding-nigeria/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The hypocrisy of the Black Lives Matter Movement]]</title><description>![CDATA[The hypocrisy of the Black Lives Matter Movement]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-21 12:30:26+00:00</pubDate><link>https://eu.examiner-enterprise.com/story/opinion/columns/2020/07/21/hypocrisy-of-black-lives-matter-movement/112696474/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://eu.examiner-enterprise.com/story/opinion/columns/2020/07/21/hypocrisy-of-black-lives-matter-movement/112696474/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Epstein case: Suspect who shot family of judge on DB-Jeffrey Epstein case found dead after apparent suicide – reports]]</title><description>![CDATA[Epstein case: Suspect who shot family of judge on DB-Jeffrey Epstein case found dead after apparent suicide – reports]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-20 19:40:28+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/495320-suspect-epstein-judge-shooting-suicide/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rt.com/usa/495320-suspect-epstein-judge-shooting-suicide/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Epstein case: Attorney who was found dead named as primary suspect in fatal shooting at federal judge’s home]]</title><description>![CDATA[Epstein case: Attorney who was found dead named as primary suspect in fatal shooting at federal judge’s home]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-19 19:38:39+00:00</pubDate><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/07/19/us/federal-judge-esther-salas-shooting-investigation/index.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://edition.cnn.com/2020/07/19/us/federal-judge-esther-salas-shooting-investigation/index.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[WEF founder: Must prepare for an angrier world]]</title><description>![CDATA[WEF founder: Must prepare for an angrier world]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-14 21:12:36+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LJTnkzl3K64</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LJTnkzl3K64</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[New BAFTA Gaming Standards are INSANE]]</title><description>![CDATA[New BAFTA Gaming Standards are INSANE]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-14 09:01:59+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dw9lmEp7Q6E</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dw9lmEp7Q6E</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[McCloskey case: Police seize gun at home of St. Louis couple who pointed weapons at protesters]]</title><description>![CDATA[McCloskey case: Police seize gun at home of St. Louis couple who pointed weapons at protesters]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-11 08:15:05+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mark-patricia-mccloskey-guns-seized-at-st-louis-home-couple-who-pointed-weapons-at-protesters/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mark-patricia-mccloskey-guns-seized-at-st-louis-home-couple-who-pointed-weapons-at-protesters/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Confessions Of A Dead Man: Personal Driver Of Jeffrey Epstein And Other Elites Tells All]]</title><description>![CDATA[Confessions Of A Dead Man: Personal Driver Of Jeffrey Epstein And Other Elites Tells All]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-10 15:28:46+00:00</pubDate><link>https://supersoldiertalk.com/confessions-of-a-dead-man-personal-driver-of-jeffrey-epstein-and-other-elites-tells-all/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://supersoldiertalk.com/confessions-of-a-dead-man-personal-driver-of-jeffrey-epstein-and-other-elites-tells-all/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Climate Change Is An Absolute Nightmare - This Is Why]]</title><description>![CDATA[Climate Change Is An Absolute Nightmare - This Is Why]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-09 07:33:22+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uqwvf6R1_QY</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uqwvf6R1_QY</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Deutsche Bank fined $150M for failing to flag Epstein's shady transactions]]</title><description>![CDATA[New York regulators fined Deutsche Bank $150 million Tuesday and slammed the lender for "mistakes and sloppiness" in its relationship with accused sex-trafficker Jeffrey Epstein.]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-07 17:23:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/07/business/jeffrey-epstein-deutsche-bank-fine/index.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/07/business/jeffrey-epstein-deutsche-bank-fine/index.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Confessions Of A Dead Man: Personal Driver Of Jeffrey Epstein And Other Elites Tells All]]</title><description>![CDATA[Confessions Of A Dead Man: Personal Driver Of Jeffrey Epstein And Other Elites Tells All]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-03 15:28:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://cloverchronicle.com/2020/07/03/confessions-of-a-dead-man-personal-driver-of-jeffrey-epstein-and-other-elites-tells-all/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cloverchronicle.com/2020/07/03/confessions-of-a-dead-man-personal-driver-of-jeffrey-epstein-and-other-elites-tells-all/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Judge Rules Virginia Giuffre's Lawyers Must 'Destroy' Jeffrey Epstein Files]]</title><description>![CDATA[Judge Rules Virginia Giuffre's Lawyers Must 'Destroy' Jeffrey Epstein Files]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-02 19:43:29+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.newsweek.com/judge-rules-virginia-giuffres-lawyers-must-destroy-jeffrey-epstein-files-1514909</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsweek.com/judge-rules-virginia-giuffres-lawyers-must-destroy-jeffrey-epstein-files-1514909</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[I built my own camera with a Raspberry Pi 4 - The Verge]]</title><description>![CDATA[I built my own camera with a Raspberry Pi 4 - The Verge]]</description><pubDate>2020-07-01 16:58:28+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theverge.com/21306907/diy-camera-raspberry-pi-high-quality-how-to-build-video-c-cs-mount-lenses</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21306907/diy-camera-raspberry-pi-high-quality-how-to-build-video-c-cs-mount-lenses</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[YouTube bans David Duke and other US far-right users]]</title><description>![CDATA[test]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-30 20:01:50+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/jun/30/youtube-bans-david-duke-and-other-us-far-right-users</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/jun/30/youtube-bans-david-duke-and-other-us-far-right-users</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[India bans TikTok, WeChat and dozens more Chinese apps - BBC News]]</title><description>![CDATA[India bans TikTok, WeChat and dozens more Chinese apps - BBC News]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-29 21:43:31+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-53225720</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-53225720</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[What is the real goal of the ‘Stop Hate for Profit’ campaign against Facebook? Hint: it has nothing to do with ‘hate speech’]]</title><description>![CDATA[What is the real goal of the ‘Stop Hate for Profit’ campaign against Facebook? Hint: it has nothing to do with ‘hate speech’]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-29 12:14:35+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.rt.com/op-ed/493295-stop-hate-advertising-extortion-astroturf/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.rt.com/op-ed/493295-stop-hate-advertising-extortion-astroturf/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Face masks: Want to prevent another shutdown, save 33,000 lives and protect yourself? Wear a face mask, doctors say | CNN]]</title><description>![CDATA[Face masks: Want to prevent another shutdown, save 33,000 lives and protect yourself? Wear a face mask, doctors say | CNN]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-29 09:48:31+00:00</pubDate><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/06/25/health/face-mask-guidance-covid-19/index.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://edition.cnn.com/2020/06/25/health/face-mask-guidance-covid-19/index.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA["Reddit will allow racist hate speech directed at ""majority"" populations and conservatives"]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-29 06:52:34+00:00</pubDate><link>https://twitter.com/TomFitton/status/1277667890913738753</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://twitter.com/TomFitton/status/1277667890913738753</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[It's probably time to stop recommending Clean Code]]</title><description>![CDATA[It's probably time to stop recommending Clean Code]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-28 09:56:27+00:00</pubDate><link>https://qntm.org/clean</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://qntm.org/clean</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Almost 300 Windows 10 executables vulnerable to DLL hijacking]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-27 06:48:07+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/almost-300-windows-10-executables-vulnerable-to-dll-hijacking/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/almost-300-windows-10-executables-vulnerable-to-dll-hijacking/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[BLM co-founder describes herself as 'trained Marxist']]</title><description>![CDATA[BLM co-founder describes herself as 'trained Marxist']]</description><pubDate>2020-06-25 21:03:29+00:00</pubDate><link>https://nypost.com/2020/06/25/blm-co-founder-describes-herself-as-trained-marxist/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://nypost.com/2020/06/25/blm-co-founder-describes-herself-as-trained-marxist/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[How do you deal with people who refuse to wear a mask? - The Verge]]</title><description>![CDATA[How do you deal with people who refuse to wear a mask? - The Verge]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-25 10:00:20+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theverge.com/21303553/face-mask-coronavirus-cdc-etiquette-public</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theverge.com/21303553/face-mask-coronavirus-cdc-etiquette-public</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[BlackRock Is Biggest Beneficiary of Fed Purchases of Corporate Bond ETFs | Barron's]]</title><description>![CDATA[BlackRock Is Biggest Beneficiary of Fed Purchases of Corporate Bond ETFs | Barron's]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-20 16:50:04+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/blackrock-is-biggest-beneficiary-of-fed-purchases-of-corporate-bond-etfs-51591034726</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.barrons.com/articles/blackrock-is-biggest-beneficiary-of-fed-purchases-of-corporate-bond-etfs-51591034726</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[What's been happening in China's Xinjiang, home to 11 million Uyghurs?]]</title><description>![CDATA[As US President Donald Trump signed a bill into law Wednesday that aims to punish Beijing for its repression of the Uyghur ethnic minority, he was accused by his former national security adviser of endorsing China's construction of internment camps in its western region of Xinjiang.]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-19 09:06:18+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/19/asia/xinjiang-explainer-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/19/asia/xinjiang-explainer-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Steam Games Pulled by Indie Devs Over Valve's Silence on Black Lives Matter]]</title><description>![CDATA[Steam Games Pulled by Indie Devs Over Valve's Silence on Black Lives Matter]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-17 08:00:19+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dualshockers.com/steam-games-pulled-indie-developers-over-valve-silence-black-lives-matter/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dualshockers.com/steam-games-pulled-indie-developers-over-valve-silence-black-lives-matter/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[John Oliver on police use of facial recognition: 'We’re about to cross a major line']]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>The Last Week Tonight host tracks the chilling expansion of facial recognition technology in the US by law enforcement and the need for regulation</p><p>John Oliver returned to the white void of at-home Last Week Tonight on Sunday with a report on facial recognition, a technology which has been around for years but whose use by law enforcement has come under renewed scrutiny as protests against anti-black racism and police brutality continue across the US.</p><p>Law enforcement is <a href="https://www.perpetuallineup.org/">one of the biggest users</a> of facial recognition in the US, Oliver explained, with <a href="https://www.perpetuallineup.org/">one study</a> finding that approximately half of all Americans have had a photo of them searched through by the police – the justification being that ethically fraught facial recognition tech may prevent terror attacks or other crimes.</p> <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2020/jun/15/john-oliver-police-use-facial-recognition">Continue reading...</a>]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-15 16:20:35+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2020/jun/15/john-oliver-police-use-facial-recognition</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2020/jun/15/john-oliver-police-use-facial-recognition</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Berlin authorities placed children with pedophiles]]</title><description>![CDATA[Berlin authorities placed children with pedophiles]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-15 07:31:10+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dw.com/en/berlin-authorities-placed-children-with-pedophiles-for-30-years/a-53814208</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dw.com/en/berlin-authorities-placed-children-with-pedophiles-for-30-years/a-53814208</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Christopher Columbus statues are being beheaded and torn down during Black Lives Matter protests]]</title><description>![CDATA[Christopher Columbus statues are being beheaded and torn down during Black Lives Matter protests]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-11 20:11:27+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.insider.com/christopher-columbus-statues-vandalized-during-protests-2020-6</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.insider.com/christopher-columbus-statues-vandalized-during-protests-2020-6</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[How To install Webmin On Raspberry Pi OS (For Remote Administration) - Smart Home Pursuits]]</title><description>![CDATA[How To install Webmin On Raspberry Pi OS (For Remote Administration) - Smart Home Pursuits]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-09 10:44:56+00:00</pubDate><link>https://smarthomepursuits.com/install-webmin-on-raspberry-pi-for-web-based-administration/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://smarthomepursuits.com/install-webmin-on-raspberry-pi-for-web-based-administration/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA['Big concerns' over Gates foundation's potential to become largest WHO donor]]</title><description>![CDATA['Big concerns' over Gates foundation's potential to become largest WHO donor]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-05 13:47:07+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.devex.com/news/big-concerns-over-gates-foundation-s-potential-to-become-largest-who-donor-97377</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.devex.com/news/big-concerns-over-gates-foundation-s-potential-to-become-largest-who-donor-97377</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Programming 'language': Brain scans reveal coding uses same regions as speech]]</title><description>![CDATA[Programming 'language': Brain scans reveal coding uses same regions as speech]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-05 09:53:34+00:00</pubDate><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-06-language-brain-scans-reveal-coding.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-06-language-brain-scans-reveal-coding.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Against Method and For 'Pseudoscience']]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>Paul Feyerabend argued for 'Epistemological Anarchism': that in order to do truly good science, one can't rule out alternative methods, <em>ad hoc</em> hypotheses, mythology, religion and wishful thinking. Using the example of Galileo, he shows how science's greatest strides are made by deliberately being "unscientific" in the way that court scientists tend to think nowadays.</p><p>Epistemological Anarchism is a total rejection of the so-called "demarcation problem": the attempt by early 20th century philosophers to distinguish "science" from other realms. It overturns the assumptions of logical positivism and returns us to the conception of knowledge held by antiquity, the scholastics, the Renaissance and everyone else: science can't rule out its perceived opponents by technicality or it would have also undermined the very "pseudoscientists" that developed us our scientific conceptions of today.</p><details>📚 See readings and other media.<p><em>Note that pay-walled academic articles may be obtained by feeding their URLs to sites like Sci-Hub.</em></p><ul><li><em>Against Method</em> (Paul Feyerabend)</li><li><em>Conjectures and Refutations</em> (Karl Popper)</li><li><em>The Structure of Scientific Revolutions</em> (Thomas Kuhn)</li><li><a href="http://www.staff.science.uu.nl/~hooft101/fringe-oct-2017.pdf">"The importance of recognising fringe science"</a> (Gerald t'Hooft)</li></ul></details><h1>More...</h1><ul><li>The <em>Not Related!</em> website: <a href="https://notrelated.xyz"></a>notrelated.xyz</a></li><li>Donations will be read in the middle of each episode: <a href="https://donate.notrelated.xyz">donate.notrelated.xyz</a></li></ul>]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-05 04:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://notrelated.xyz/audio/s02/S02E01_-_Against_Method_and_For_Pseudoscience.ogg</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://notrelated.xyz/audio/s02/S02E01_-_Against_Method_and_For_Pseudoscience.ogg</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The 10 Commitments Companies Must Make to Advance Racial Justice]]</title><description>![CDATA[The 10 Commitments Companies Must Make to Advance Racial Justice]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-04 09:12:09+00:00</pubDate><link>https://hbr.org/2020/06/the-10-commitments-companies-must-make-to-advance-racial-justice</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://hbr.org/2020/06/the-10-commitments-companies-must-make-to-advance-racial-justice</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Blizzard Called Out For BLM Protest Support After Blitzchung Hong Kong Controversy]]</title><description>![CDATA[Blizzard Called Out For BLM Protest Support After Blitzchung Hong Kong Controversy]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-03 12:11:41+00:00</pubDate><link>https://screenrant.com/blizzard-protest-blackout-black-lives-matter-hong-kong/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://screenrant.com/blizzard-protest-blackout-black-lives-matter-hong-kong/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[US Senators Introduce 'Lawful Access to Encrypted Data Act' - With Backdoor Mandate]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-06-02 12:26:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://news.bitcoin.com/lawful-access-to-encrypted-data-act-backdoor/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.bitcoin.com/lawful-access-to-encrypted-data-act-backdoor/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Ricky Gervais – Golden Globes 2020 (Uncensored, HD)]]</title><description>![CDATA[Ricky Gervais – Golden Globes 2020 (Uncensored, HD)]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-29 07:20:46+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iJOb9xHggS4</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iJOb9xHggS4</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Roko's Basilisk: The Most Terrifying Thought Experiment]]</title><description>![CDATA[Roko's Basilisk: The Most Terrifying Thought Experiment]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-28 21:22:21+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ut-zGHLAVLI</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ut-zGHLAVLI</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Study: Up to 80% of COVID-19 Infections Are Asymptomatic | Time]]</title><description>![CDATA[Study: Up to 80% of COVID-19 Infections Are Asymptomatic | Time]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-27 19:48:09+00:00</pubDate><link>https://time.com/5842669/coronavirus-asymptomatic-transmission/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://time.com/5842669/coronavirus-asymptomatic-transmission/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[BlackRock: Unofficial Fourth Arm Of Government | The WealthAdvisor]]</title><description>![CDATA[BlackRock: Unofficial Fourth Arm Of Government | The WealthAdvisor]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-22 22:39:57+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.thewealthadvisor.com/article/blackrock-unofficial-fourth-arm-government</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thewealthadvisor.com/article/blackrock-unofficial-fourth-arm-government</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Face mask rules more political than scientific, says expert]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>Study reveals cloth coverings reduce airflow but Covid-19 effectiveness remains unproven</p><ul><li><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/series/coronavirus-live/latest">Coronavirus – latest updates</a></li><li><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/coronavirus-outbreak">See all our coronavirus coverage</a></li></ul><p>The wearing of cloth face masks by the public was becoming more about politics than science, one expert has argued, as a new study reveals potential benefits and problems of the coverings.</p><p>At present the UK government recommends <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/may/11/public-advised-wear-face-masks-coronavirus-lockdown-easing-plan-for-england">the public wear face coverings</a> when in crowded places where it is not always possible to maintain social distancing – a stance also taken by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) – while other countries, <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/30/czechs-get-to-work-making-masks-after-government-decree-coronavirus">including the Czech Republic</a>, have made the wearing of masks in the community mandatory.</p> <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2020/may/21/face-mask-rules-more-political-than-scientific-says-expert">Continue reading...</a>]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-20 23:01:39+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2020/may/21/face-mask-rules-more-political-than-scientific-says-expert</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2020/may/21/face-mask-rules-more-political-than-scientific-says-expert</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Where New Yorkers Moved to Escape Coronavirus - The New York Times]]</title><description>![CDATA[Where New Yorkers Moved to Escape Coronavirus - The New York Times]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-16 20:09:25+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/05/16/nyregion/nyc-coronavirus-moving-leaving.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/05/16/nyregion/nyc-coronavirus-moving-leaving.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[More than 100,000 small businesses have permanently closed due to coronavirus, study estimates – The Hill]]</title><description>![CDATA[More than 100,000 small businesses have permanently closed due to coronavirus, study estimates – The Hill]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-13 20:41:10+00:00</pubDate><link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/longevity/497519-more-than-100000-small-businesses-have-permanently/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/longevity/497519-more-than-100000-small-businesses-have-permanently/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[SMS Two-Factor Authentication – Worse Than Just a Good Password? | Okta Security]]</title><description>![CDATA[SMS Two-Factor Authentication – Worse Than Just a Good Password? | Okta Security]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-13 06:56:06+00:00</pubDate><link>https://sec.okta.com/articles/2020/05/sms-two-factor-authentication-worse-just-good-password</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sec.okta.com/articles/2020/05/sms-two-factor-authentication-worse-just-good-password</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Why Would the US Have Funded the Controversial Wuhan Lab?]]</title><description>![CDATA[Why Would the US Have Funded the Controversial Wuhan Lab?]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-13 06:52:14+00:00</pubDate><link>https://thediplomat.com/2020/05/why-would-the-us-have-funded-the-controversial-wuhan-lab/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://thediplomat.com/2020/05/why-would-the-us-have-funded-the-controversial-wuhan-lab/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Politics matters most to slaves.]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>Now onto the second point I didn't get to <a href="https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/why-do-i-so-rarely-talk-about-politics-on-my-channel">in my post
yesterday</a>:
politics only matters so much when you're a slave. Or as I put it
there, &quot;You will need politics less than you think.&quot;</p>
<p>That is to say that if you live in a city where your every action is
watched, if you use proprietary software and communicate only via social
media services, if you have no marketable skills because you have some
inert degree and questionably productive and definitely replaceable job
and a large company, you need politics quite a great deal.</p>
<p>Your entire existence in the system is based on being a good boy within
the established boundaries of what is deemed by the mass media to be
socio-politically appropriate. <em>Maybe</em> you've gone into debt, but you
<em>definitely</em> rely the whole &quot;system&quot; for all the basics. If you don't
think you do, just ask yourself whether your life has changed for the
better after the Coronachan Panic of 2020.</p>
<p>What's the alternative? Well, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LRVmfx4EWI0">boomer rants viewers might see some of
this coming</a>...</p>
<p>The fact of the matter is that both the daily ins-and-outs of politics
and the overarching trends of politics matter very little the more
independent your are of the system. Earlier, I always mumbled about how
conservaboomers seemed a little too apathetic about the cultural changes
being forced on them. This social engineering still is the most serious
problem in all technologically-complex mass-media societies, but I must
admit for people who choose personal independence and independence for
their families and local communities, it is much less of a problem.</p>
<p>When I was plugged into the system, minorly red-pilled and generally
peeved because I actually paid attention to the media as something other
than to laugh at, I found the idea of Political &quot;Exit&quot; pretty cucky.
How much sense does it make to leave the &quot;political process&quot;
altogether? Sounds like giving up.</p>
<p>It sounds like giving up because the &quot;political process&quot; is something
internal to the media system at large. That's why even when the
political process does something the media doesn't like (like electing
the Orange Boomer, for example), its actions are immediately rendered
inert by fakery.</p>
<p>The actual solution is creating and participating in organic society,
which still very much exists outside the purview of the media and NGOs
and the like. People still need plumbers. No one is going to fire a
plumber because he says trannies are mentally ill men in
dresses&mdash;otherwise there'd be no plumbers. Or electricians, or
builders or anyone who actually does anything productive. It'd just be
HR, journalists and professors left... and some open source developers
who write more codes of conducts than they do software. Do you think
they'll be able to feed you?</p>
<p>Exiting the system is actually the opposite of surrender. Why would you
think the solution is something like voting or even &quot;owning the libs&quot;
or something publicly advertised as a solution? The actual solution is
building an alternative. Or maybe <em>rebuilding</em> the alternative.</p>
<p>Do you really want to make your boss rich if you think he'd turn around
and betray you because of a media witchhunt? It's better for you to be
doxxed and fired now rather than wait 20 years for it, getting more
ensconced in the insanity. Start becoming more independent now.</p>
<p>A lot of people LARP about what they're going to do when they take over
&quot;the system&quot; by revolution. Revolution, the idea of abrupt enforced
change, however, is fundamentally their idea and if you buy it, you're
going to keep running your head into a wall.</p>
<p>Being independent, living out of the city and the Matrix, however, is
simultaneously like transporting yourself back in time to when things
were saner, but at the same time, transporting yourself into the future
where &quot;the system&quot; has already collapsed and we're already
rebuilding. Be a part of it now rather than later.</p>]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-09 00:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/politics-matters-most-to-slaves/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://lukesmith.xyz/articles/politics-matters-most-to-slaves/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[U.S. Field Hospitals Stand Down, Most Without Treating Any COVID-19 Patients]]</title><description>![CDATA[U.S. Field Hospitals Stand Down, Most Without Treating Any COVID-19 Patients]]</description><pubDate>2020-05-07 21:04:58+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.npr.org/2020/05/07/851712311/u-s-field-hospitals-stand-down-most-without-treating-any-covid-19-patients?t=1609407487809</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/05/07/851712311/u-s-field-hospitals-stand-down-most-without-treating-any-covid-19-patients?t=1609407487809</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Dr. Fauci Backed Controversial Wuhan Lab with U.S. Dollars for Risky Coronavirus Research]]</title><description>![CDATA[Dr. Fauci Backed Controversial Wuhan Lab with U.S. Dollars for Risky Coronavirus Research]]</description><pubDate>2020-04-28 20:20:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.newsweek.com/dr-fauci-backed-controversial-wuhan-lab-millions-us-dollars-risky-coronavirus-research-1500741</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.newsweek.com/dr-fauci-backed-controversial-wuhan-lab-millions-us-dollars-risky-coronavirus-research-1500741</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Amazon uses data from third-party sellers to develop its own products, WSJ investigation finds]]</title><description>![CDATA[]]</description><pubDate>2020-04-23 14:07:06+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/04/23/wsj-amazon-uses-data-from-third-party-sellers-to-develop-its-own-products.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cnbc.com/2020/04/23/wsj-amazon-uses-data-from-third-party-sellers-to-develop-its-own-products.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Wuhan lab says there's no way coronavirus originated there. Here's the science.]]</title><description>![CDATA[Wuhan lab says there's no way coronavirus originated there. Here's the science.]]</description><pubDate>2020-04-18 06:52:28+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.livescience.com/coronavirus-wuhan-lab-complicated-origins.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.livescience.com/coronavirus-wuhan-lab-complicated-origins.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[3 Undeniable Reasons Why You Need Online Anonymity]]</title><description>![CDATA[3 Undeniable Reasons Why You Need Online Anonymity]]</description><pubDate>2020-04-03 07:49:34+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.makeuseof.com/tag/3-undeniable-reasons-need-online-anonymity/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.makeuseof.com/tag/3-undeniable-reasons-need-online-anonymity/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Bodies are being left in the streets in an overwhelmed Ecuadorian city]]</title><description>![CDATA[Bodies are being left in the streets in an overwhelmed Ecuadorian city]]</description><pubDate>2020-04-03 07:26:22+00:00</pubDate><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2020/04/03/americas/guayaquil-ecuador-overwhelmed-coronavirus-intl/index.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://edition.cnn.com/2020/04/03/americas/guayaquil-ecuador-overwhelmed-coronavirus-intl/index.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Whistleblowing coronavirus doctor mysteriously vanishes]]</title><description>![CDATA[Whistleblowing coronavirus doctor mysteriously vanishes]]</description><pubDate>2020-04-01 20:29:25+00:00</pubDate><link>https://nypost.com/2020/04/01/whistleblowing-coronavirus-doctor-mysteriously-vanishes/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://nypost.com/2020/04/01/whistleblowing-coronavirus-doctor-mysteriously-vanishes/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Misused photo of migrants’ coffins used to cast doubt on Covid-19 in Italy]]</title><description>![CDATA[Misused photo of migrants’ coffins used to cast doubt on Covid-19 in Italy]]</description><pubDate>2020-04-01 07:43:17+00:00</pubDate><link>https://observers.france24.com/en/europe/20220106-debunked-covid-19-migrant-coffins-documentary-bergamo</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://observers.france24.com/en/europe/20220106-debunked-covid-19-migrant-coffins-documentary-bergamo</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Are You a Slave to your Software Knowledge?]]</title><description>![CDATA[Are You a Slave to your Software Knowledge?]]</description><pubDate>2020-03-31 09:10:22+00:00</pubDate><link>https://sagegerard.com/stop-learning-so-much.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sagegerard.com/stop-learning-so-much.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[NYC's Footprint Amid The COVID-19 Outbreak]]</title><description>![CDATA[NYC's Footprint Amid The COVID-19 Outbreak]]</description><pubDate>2020-03-26 20:00:02+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q5BFrDocPNs</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q5BFrDocPNs</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The Fed Asks for BlackRock’s Help in an Echo of 2008 - The New York Times]]</title><description>![CDATA[The Fed Asks for BlackRock’s Help in an Echo of 2008 - The New York Times]]</description><pubDate>2020-03-25 22:38:13+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/25/business/blackrock-federal-reserve.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/25/business/blackrock-federal-reserve.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Yuval Noah Harari: the world after coronavirus | Free to read]]</title><description>![CDATA[Yuval Noah Harari: the world after coronavirus | Free to read]]</description><pubDate>2020-03-20 14:11:41+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.ft.com/content/19d90308-6858-11ea-a3c9-1fe6fedcca75#comments-anchor</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ft.com/content/19d90308-6858-11ea-a3c9-1fe6fedcca75#comments-anchor</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[An assistant professor says he was fired because he dared to talk about human population variation and got slandered as a eugenicist.]]</title><description>![CDATA[An assistant professor says he was fired because he dared to talk about human population variation and got slandered as a eugenicist.]]</description><pubDate>2020-03-12 20:05:49+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.insidehighered.com/news/2020/03/12/assistant-professor-says-hes-been-fired-because-he-dared-talk-about-human-population</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.insidehighered.com/news/2020/03/12/assistant-professor-says-hes-been-fired-because-he-dared-talk-about-human-population</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Surgeon General Urges the Public to Stop Buying Face Masks - The New York Times]]</title><description>![CDATA[Surgeon General Urges the Public to Stop Buying Face Masks - The New York Times]]</description><pubDate>2020-02-29 15:28:58+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/29/health/coronavirus-n95-face-masks.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/29/health/coronavirus-n95-face-masks.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Your smart speaker could be listening in on your conversations by accident]]</title><description>![CDATA[Your smart speaker could be listening in on your conversations by accident]]</description><pubDate>2020-02-26 20:50:35+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.techradar.com/news/your-smart-speaker-could-be-accidentally-listening-in-on-your-conversations</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.techradar.com/news/your-smart-speaker-could-be-accidentally-listening-in-on-your-conversations</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[BlackRock’s black box: the technology hub of modern finance - Financial Times | Busi Buggy]]</title><description>![CDATA[BlackRock’s black box: the technology hub of modern finance - Financial Times | Busi Buggy]]</description><pubDate>2020-02-23 22:16:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://busibuggy.blogspot.com/2020/02/blackrocks-black-box-technology-hub-of.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://busibuggy.blogspot.com/2020/02/blackrocks-black-box-technology-hub-of.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Sophie Lewis Is Reviving the Case for Abolishing the Family]]</title><description>![CDATA[Sophie Lewis Is Reviving the Case for Abolishing the Family]]</description><pubDate>2020-02-21 21:54:24+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjdzwb/sophie-lewis-feminist-abolishing-the-family-full-surrogacy-now</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjdzwb/sophie-lewis-feminist-abolishing-the-family-full-surrogacy-now</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Why YOUTUBE is DYING (Creatively and Artistically)]]</title><description>![CDATA[Why YOUTUBE is DYING (Creatively and Artistically)]]</description><pubDate>2020-02-17 20:52:51+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ln1qbgZz_TQ</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ln1qbgZz_TQ</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[UK police deny responsibility for poster urging parents to report kids for using Kali Linux | ZDNET]]</title><description>![CDATA[UK police deny responsibility for poster urging parents to report kids for using Kali Linux | ZDNET]]</description><pubDate>2020-02-14 21:03:32+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/uk-police-distance-themselves-from-poster-warning-parents-to-report-kids-for-using-kali-linux/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.zdnet.com/article/uk-police-distance-themselves-from-poster-warning-parents-to-report-kids-for-using-kali-linux/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Facebook, Amazon, Google and more met with WHO to figure out how to stop coronavirus misinformation]]</title><description>![CDATA[Facebook, Amazon, Google and more met with WHO to figure out how to stop coronavirus misinformation]]</description><pubDate>2020-02-14 13:01:29+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/14/facebook-google-amazon-met-with-who-to-talk-coronavirus-misinformation.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/14/facebook-google-amazon-met-with-who-to-talk-coronavirus-misinformation.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Becoming a Technical Leader]]</title><description>![CDATA[Becoming a Technical Leader]]</description><pubDate>2020-02-12 09:13:20+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/becoming-technical-leader-michael-vanhoutte/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/becoming-technical-leader-michael-vanhoutte/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Texas mother trying to transition her seven-year-old son into a girl loses in court as judge orders her to share custody with ex-husband who says boy is just 'confused']]</title><description>![CDATA[Texas mother trying to transition her seven-year-old son into a girl loses in court as judge orders her to share custody with ex-husband who says boy is just 'confused']]</description><pubDate>2020-01-31 08:51:05+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7950655/Mother-trying-transition-son-girl-loses-court-judge-orders-parents-joint-custody.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7950655/Mother-trying-transition-son-girl-loses-court-judge-orders-parents-joint-custody.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Coronavirus Outbreak: Man lies dead on a street in China]]</title><description>![CDATA[Coronavirus Outbreak: Man lies dead on a street in China]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-31 07:48:27+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CYKeefzKGOI</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CYKeefzKGOI</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[A man lies dead in the street: the image that captures the Wuhan coronavirus crisis]]</title><description>![CDATA[A man lies dead in the street: the image that captures the Wuhan coronavirus crisis]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-31 07:24:23+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/jan/31/a-man-lies-dead-in-the-street-the-image-that-captures-the-wuhan-coronavirus-crisis</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/jan/31/a-man-lies-dead-in-the-street-the-image-that-captures-the-wuhan-coronavirus-crisis</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Australia defends plan to create island quarantine camp | AP News]]</title><description>![CDATA[Australia defends plan to create island quarantine camp | AP News]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-30 20:15:13+00:00</pubDate><link>https://apnews.com/c129280f6ab2a832908b8dcf4888364b</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://apnews.com/c129280f6ab2a832908b8dcf4888364b</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Disturbing Footages Show People Collapsing in Virus-Hit Chinese City of Wuhan]]</title><description>![CDATA[Disturbing Footages Show People Collapsing in Virus-Hit Chinese City of Wuhan]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-24 07:54:11+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.tasnimnews.com/en/news/2020/01/24/2188257/disturbing-footages-show-people-collapsing-in-virus-hit-chinese-city-of-wuhan</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.tasnimnews.com/en/news/2020/01/24/2188257/disturbing-footages-show-people-collapsing-in-virus-hit-chinese-city-of-wuhan</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The Secretive Company That Might End Privacy as We Know It - The New York Times]]</title><description>![CDATA[The Secretive Company That Might End Privacy as We Know It - The New York Times]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-18 19:58:54+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/18/technology/clearview-privacy-facial-recognition.html</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/18/technology/clearview-privacy-facial-recognition.html</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[COVID-19 pandemic]]</title><description>![CDATA[COVID-19 pandemic]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-16 11:26:30+00:00</pubDate><link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/COVID-19_pandemic#History</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/COVID-19_pandemic#History</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Facebook Glitch Reveals Greta Thunberg’s Posts Are Written by Her Father: Report]]</title><description>![CDATA[Facebook Glitch Reveals Greta Thunberg’s Posts Are Written by Her Father: Report]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-14 19:00:28+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2020/01/facebook-glitch-reveals-greta-thunbergs-posts-are-written-by-her-father-report/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2020/01/facebook-glitch-reveals-greta-thunbergs-posts-are-written-by-her-father-report/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Facebook Glitch Reveals Father, Activist Behind Greta Thunberg’s Facebook Page. Greta Responds.]]</title><description>![CDATA[Facebook Glitch Reveals Father, Activist Behind Greta Thunberg’s Facebook Page. Greta Responds.]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-13 19:01:16+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/facebook-glitch-reveals-father-activist-behind-greta-thunbergs-facebook-page-greta-responds</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dailywire.com/news/facebook-glitch-reveals-father-activist-behind-greta-thunbergs-facebook-page-greta-responds</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Anger over use of facial recognition at south Wales football derby]]</title><description>![CDATA[<p>Protest held before Cardiff v Swansea as fans say technology is taking away their rights</p><p>Football supporters and civil rights activists have expressed anger and concern over the use of facial recognition technology for a derby match in south Wales.</p><p>Two surveillance vans kitted out with the controversial technology were seen patrolling around Cardiff City’s stadium before the club’s game against Swansea City on Sunday.</p> <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/jan/12/anger-over-use-facial-recognition-south-wales-football-derby-cardiff-swansea">Continue reading...</a>]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-12 14:05:26+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/jan/12/anger-over-use-facial-recognition-south-wales-football-derby-cardiff-swansea</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/jan/12/anger-over-use-facial-recognition-south-wales-football-derby-cardiff-swansea</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Ring Fired Employees for Watching Customer Videos]]</title><description>![CDATA[Ring Fired Employees for Watching Customer Videos]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-08 12:16:22+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3mdvk/ring-fired-employees-abusing-video-data</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3mdvk/ring-fired-employees-abusing-video-data</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[New Virus Discovered by Chinese Scientists Investigating Pneumonia Outbreak]]</title><description>![CDATA[New Virus Discovered by Chinese Scientists Investigating Pneumonia Outbreak]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-08 07:50:34+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-virus-discovered-by-chinese-scientists-investigating-pneumonia-outbreak-11578485668?mod=article_inline</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-virus-discovered-by-chinese-scientists-investigating-pneumonia-outbreak-11578485668?mod=article_inline</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Joe Rogan on Ricky Gervais' Golden Globes Monologue]]</title><description>![CDATA[Joe Rogan on Ricky Gervais' Golden Globes Monologue]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-07 07:37:49+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WRbaQrb3Jhk</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WRbaQrb3Jhk</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[A Look Inside Jeffrey Epstein’s Prison Cell]]</title><description>![CDATA[A Look Inside Jeffrey Epstein’s Prison Cell]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-05 12:15:41+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.thecrimemag.com/epsteins-prison-cell/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thecrimemag.com/epsteins-prison-cell/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Why Stakeholder Capitalism Will Fail]]</title><description>![CDATA[Why Stakeholder Capitalism Will Fail]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-05 08:54:26+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stevedenning/2020/01/05/why-stakeholder-capitalism-will-fail/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.forbes.com/sites/stevedenning/2020/01/05/why-stakeholder-capitalism-will-fail/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[Who’s Really Responsible for Climate Change?]]</title><description>![CDATA[Who’s Really Responsible for Climate Change?]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-02 14:33:49+00:00</pubDate><link>https://harvardpolitics.com/climate-change-responsibility/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://harvardpolitics.com/climate-change-responsibility/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[80-characters-per-line limits should be terminal, says Linux kernel chief Linus Torvalds]]</title><description>![CDATA[80-characters-per-line limits should be terminal, says Linux kernel chief Linus Torvalds]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-01 13:56:53+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.theregister.com/2020/06/01/linux_5_7/</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theregister.com/2020/06/01/linux_5_7/</guid>
<item><title>![CDATA[The Turning Point]]</title><description>![CDATA['The Turning Point' explores the destruction of the environment, climate change and species extinction from different perspective. Music by Wantaways. 

Created in After Effects, Premiere Pro, Clip Studio Pro and Cinema 4D. 

Written, directed and animated by Steve Cutts

Support me here: https://www.buymeacoffee.com/stevecutts

Follow me here:
https://www.instagram.com/steve_cutts_official
https://www.facebook.com/SteveCuttsArt/ 
www.stevecutts.com

Music by Wantaways
► Stream song on Spotify:  https://open.spotify.com/track/6Or84r7sBRNO4WBep52I4k?si=8NS9h4jUQ3SeZzUZJ7_3QQ  
► Download song on iTunes:    https://music.apple.com/au/album/the-turning-point-single/1476473270  

► Subscribe to Wantaways on YouTube: http://bit.ly/WantawaysYT
► Stream song on Soundcloud: https://soundcloud.com/wantaways/the-turning-point

THE TURNING POINT Song Lyrics

My heart is free
My heart is free
No place where I would rather be

My heart is free
My heart is free
Until you come to rescue me

You find me here
You find me here
You dry my eyes and shed a tear
You turn me bad
You turn me good
Forget to hope and learn to fear

CHORUS

Tell me that its good
If we do something
Believe in something
I don't think I should
If it aint nothing
If it aint nothing good

My heart is free
My heart is free
No place where I would rather be 
You find me here
You find me here
You dry my eyes and shed a tear


CHORUS]]</description><pubDate>2020-01-01 00:00:00+00:00</pubDate><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p7LDk4D3Q3U</link></item><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p7LDk4D3Q3U</guid>

</channel></rss>
